[{"qid": "inter_ua_1", "question": "Who has been one of the head of government of United States of America and also the father of Tolui?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_2", "question": "Who has been one of the head of government of East Timor and also the father of Jorge Alessandri?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_3", "question": "Who has been one of the head of government of Walloon Region and also the father of Eduardo Frei Ruiz-Tagle?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_4", "question": "Who has been one of the head of government of Switzerland and also the father of Ramesses IV?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_5", "question": "Who has been one of the head of government of Chad and also the father of Ramesses VIII?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_6", "question": "Who has been one of the head of government of Hungary and also the father of Ramesses VI?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_7", "question": "Who has been one of the head of government of Denmark and also the father of Eduard Einstein?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_8", "question": "Who has been one of the head of government of Mechelen and also the father of Eugene Chaplin?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_9", "question": "Who has been one of the head of government of Vaulx-en-Velin and also the father of Indira Gandhi?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_10", "question": "Who has been one of the head of government of Netherlands and also the father of Pedro Montt?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_11", "question": "Who has been one of the head of government of Pau and also the father of Yakov Dzhugashvili?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_12", "question": "Who has been one of the head of government of Russian Soviet Federative Socialist Republic and also the father of Ramdas Gandhi?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_13", "question": "Who has been one of the head of government of Tongeren and also the father of Gordian II?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_14", "question": "Who has been one of the head of government of Bangladesh and also the father of Hadrian?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_15", "question": "Who has been one of the head of government of First Drees cabinet and also the father of Maria II of Portugal?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_16", "question": "Who has been one of the head of government of Verhofstadt I Government and also the father of Svetlana Alliluyeva?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_17", "question": "Who has been one of the head of government of Democratic Federal Yugoslavia and also the father of Trajan?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_18", "question": "Who has been one of the head of government of Brazil and also the father of Romulus?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_19", "question": "Who has been one of the head of government of Cambrai and also the father of Franz Xaver Wolfgang Mozart?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_20", "question": "Who has been one of the head of government of Slovakia and also the father of Barbara Bush?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_21", "question": "Who has been one of the head of government of Singapore and also the mother of Ptolemy IX Lathyros?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_22", "question": "Who has been one of the head of government of Turkey and also the mother of Ptolemy X Alexander I?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_23", "question": "Who has been one of the head of government of Kyiv and also the mother of Ptolemy VIII Physcon?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_24", "question": "Who has been one of the head of government of Berlusconi IV Cabinet and also the mother of Benigno Aquino III?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_25", "question": "Who has been one of the head of government of Miranda and also the mother of Jesus?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_26", "question": "Who has been one of the head of government of Villavaliente and also the mother of Anne Frank?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_27", "question": "Who has been one of the head of government of Poland and also the mother of Bart Simpson?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_28", "question": "Who has been one of the head of government of South Sudan and also the mother of Tim Berners-Lee?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_29", "question": "Who has been one of the head of government of Dubai and also the mother of Cleopatra III of Egypt?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_30", "question": "Who has been one of the head of government of India and also the mother of Berenice IV of Egypt?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_31", "question": "Who has been one of the head of government of Second Drees cabinet and also the mother of Ptolemy IV Philopator?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_32", "question": "Who has been one of the head of government of Drees-Van Schaik cabinet and also the mother of Ptolemy XII Auletes?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_33", "question": "Who has been one of the head of government of XV Constitutional Government of Portugal and also the mother of Ptolemy VII Neos Philopator?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_34", "question": "Who has been one of the head of government of Brown ministry and also the mother of Ptolemy V Epiphanes?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_35", "question": "Who has been one of the head of government of Third Drees cabinet and also the mother of Arsinoe III of Egypt?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_36", "question": "Who has been one of the head of government of Emirate of Dubai and also the mother of Paul I of Russia?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_37", "question": "Who has been one of the head of government of Duchies of Silesia and also the mother of Margot Frank?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_38", "question": "Who has been one of the head of government of Bavaria and also the mother of Lisa Simpson?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_39", "question": "Who has been one of the head of government of New York and also the mother of Cleopatra IV of Egypt?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_40", "question": "Who has been one of the head of government of Sicily and also the mother of Ptolemy XI Alexander II?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_41", "question": "Who has been the head of government of Saint Vincent and the Grenadines and also the spouse of Julia the Elder?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_42", "question": "Who has been the head of government of National People's Army and also the spouse of Ann Druyan?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_43", "question": "Who has been the head of government of Ayrault Cabinet I and also the spouse of Michelle Obama?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_44", "question": "Who has been the head of government of 28th Canadian Ministry and also the spouse of Hillary Clinton?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_45", "question": "Who has been the head of government of German Democratic Republic and also the spouse of Queen Paola of Belgium?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_46", "question": "Who has been the head of government of Samoa and also the spouse of Cleopatra II of Egypt?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_47", "question": "Who has been the head of government of Brunei and also the spouse of Mileva Marić?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_48", "question": "Who has been the head of government of Santa Lucia and also the spouse of Edith Tolkien?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_49", "question": "Who has been the head of government of United Arab Emirates and also the spouse of Paulette Goddard?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_50", "question": "Who has been the head of government of Weimar Republic and also the spouse of Nadezhda Krupskaya?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_51", "question": "Who has been the head of government of Cabinet of Serbia 2007-8 and also the spouse of Tiberius?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_52", "question": "Who has been the head of government of Santa Cruz de Bezana and also the spouse of Lotte Ulbricht?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_53", "question": "Who has been the head of government of Goebbels cabinet and also the spouse of Princess Hermine Reuss of Greiz?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_54", "question": "Who has been the head of government of Petr Nečas's Cabinet and also the spouse of Louis VIII of France?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_55", "question": "Who has been the head of government of Nicaragua and also the spouse of Carla Bruni?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_56", "question": "Who has been the head of government of Second Salmond ministry and also the spouse of Ptolemy XIII Theos Philopator?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_57", "question": "Who has been the head of government of Berlusconi III Cabinet and also the spouse of Ptolemy XIV of Egypt?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_58", "question": "Who has been the head of government of Arhavi and also the spouse of Minna Planer?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_59", "question": "Who has been the head of government of Democratic Kampuchea and also the spouse of Cosima Wagner?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_60", "question": "Who has been the head of government of Maurya empire and also the spouse of Constanze Mozart?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_61", "question": "Who has been both the head of government of Włodawa and also the head of state of United States of America?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_62", "question": "Who has been both the head of government of North German Confederation and also the head of state of Norway?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_63", "question": "Who has been both the head of government of First Merkel cabinet and also the head of state of Canada?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_64", "question": "Who has been both the head of government of Esko Aho's cabinet and also the head of state of Spain?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_65", "question": "Who has been both the head of government of Afghan Interim Administration and also the head of state of Austria?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_66", "question": "Who has been both the head of government of Mussolini Cabinet and also the head of state of Scotland?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_67", "question": "Who has been both the head of government of Cabinet of Serbia 2004-2007 and also the head of state of England?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_68", "question": "Who has been both the head of government of Paavo Lipponen's second Cabinet and also the head of state of Belgium?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_69", "question": "Who has been both the head of government of Dominica and also the head of state of Nazi Germany?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_70", "question": "Who has been both the head of government of Israel and also the head of state of Netherlands?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_71", "question": "Who has been both the head of government of Paavo Lipponen's first cabinet and also the head of state of Republic of Ireland?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_72", "question": "Who has been both the head of government of Provisional government of Israel and also the head of state of Laos?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_73", "question": "Who has been both the head of government of First government of Israel and also the head of state of Sweden?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_74", "question": "Who has been both the head of government of Third government of Israel and also the head of state of Wales?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_75", "question": "Who has been both the head of government of Seventh government of Israel and also the head of state of Greenland?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_76", "question": "Who has been both the head of government of Second government of Israel and also the head of state of Ashoka?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_77", "question": "Who has been both the head of government of Valls Cabinet I and also the head of state of Germany?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_78", "question": "Who has been both the head of government of Government of Manuel Valls II and also the head of state of Switzerland?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_79", "question": "Who has been both the head of government of Third Blair ministry and also the head of state of Russia?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_80", "question": "Who has been both the head of government of Second term of Tung Chee-hwa as Chief Executive of Hong Kong and also the head of state of Kenya?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_81", "question": "Who has been the head of government of First Major ministry and also the child of Arturo Alessandri?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_82", "question": "Who has been the head of government of Communauté d'agglomération de l'Ouest Rhodanien and also the child of Nerva?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_83", "question": "Who has been the head of government of First term of Tung Chee-hwa as Chief Executive of Hong Kong and also the child of Virgin Mary?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_84", "question": "Who has been the head of government of Weißenburg-Gunzenhausen and also the child of Carlota Joaquina of Spain?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_85", "question": "Who has been the head of government of Twenty-seventh government of Israel and also the child of Keke Geladze?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_86", "question": "Who has been the head of government of Thirty-second government of Israel and also the child of Jupiter?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_87", "question": "Who has been the head of government of Confederation of Norwegian Enterprise and also the child of Francisco Antonio Pinto?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_88", "question": "Who has been the head of government of Nagasaki Prefecture and also the child of Jawaharlal Nehru?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_89", "question": "Who has been the head of government of Second Merkel cabinet and also the child of Julius Caesar?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_90", "question": "Who has been the head of government of Cabinet Schröder I and also the child of Marcus Aurelius?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_91", "question": "Who has been the head of government of First term of Donald Tsang as Chief Executive of Hong Kong and also the child of George H. W. Bush?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_92", "question": "Who has been the head of government of Li Keqiang Government and also the child of Trajan?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_93", "question": "Who has been the head of government of Eritrea and also the child of Claudius?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_94", "question": "Who has been the head of government of Galactic Empire and also the child of Hadrian?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_95", "question": "Who has been the head of government of Iwate Prefecture and also the child of Cleopatra V of Egypt?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_96", "question": "Who has been the head of government of Gabon and also the child of Ptolemy XII Auletes?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_97", "question": "Who has been the head of government of Fourth cabinet of Napoleon III and also the child of Frederick III, German Emperor?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_98", "question": "Who has been the head of government of Russian Socialist Federative Soviet Republic and also the child of Gordian II?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_99", "question": "Who has been the head of government of First cabinet of Louis Napoleon and also the child of Mars?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_100", "question": "Who has been the head of government of Second cabinet of Louis Napoleon and also the child of Lucius Aemilius Paullus Macedonicus?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_101", "question": "Who has been the head of government of Kingdom of Denmark and also the author of The Hitchhiker's Guide to the Galaxy pentalogy?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_102", "question": "Who has been the head of government of Germany and also the author of Life, the Universe and Everything?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_103", "question": "Who has been the head of government of Russian Republic and also the author of Mostly Harmless?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_104", "question": "Who has been the head of government of 7th arrondissement of Paris and also the author of The Audacity of Hope?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_105", "question": "Who has been the head of government of Second Major ministry and also the author of Executive Order 13535?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_106", "question": "Who has been the head of government of Communauté d'agglomération Pau Béarn Pyrénées and also the author of Executive Order 13526?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_107", "question": "Who has been the head of government of First Blair Ministry and also the author of The Hitchhiker's Guide to the Galaxy?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_108", "question": "Who has been the head of government of Callaghan ministry and also the author of Gettysburg Address?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_109", "question": "Who has been the head of government of Second Blair Ministry and also the author of The Hitchhiker's Guide to the Galaxy Tertiary to Quintessential Phases?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_110", "question": "Who has been the head of government of Xi Jinping Government and also the author of Dirk Gently's Holistic Detective Agency?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_111", "question": "Who has been the head of government of Kingdom of the Netherlands and also the author of The Restaurant at the End of the Universe?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_112", "question": "Who has been the head of government of Cabinet Bismarck and also the author of The Meaning of Liff?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_113", "question": "Who has been the head of government of Obterre and also the author of Starship Titanic?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_114", "question": "Who has been the head of government of Cabinet of Helle Thorning-Schmidt and also the author of Last Chance to See?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_115", "question": "Who has been the head of government of Reichsgau Sudetenland and also the author of So Long, and Thanks for All the Fish?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_116", "question": "Who has been the head of government of Dominion of India and also the author of Dreams from My Father?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_117", "question": "Who has been the head of government of Cameron–Clegg coalition and also the author of Google Translate?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_118", "question": "Who has been the head of government of Nakhchivan Autonomous Republic and also the author of George Washington's Farewell Address?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_119", "question": "Who has been the head of government of Seventeenth government of Israel and also the author of Un cheval dans la salle de bains?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_120", "question": "Who has been the head of government of Twenty-fifth government of Israel and also the author of Google Patents?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_121", "question": "Who has been both the head of government of Second Hatta Cabinet and also the director of Kick-Ass?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_122", "question": "Who has been both the head of government of Tenth government of Israel and also the director of Modern Times?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_123", "question": "Who has been both the head of government of thirty-third government of Israel and also the director of Twin Peaks?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_124", "question": "Who has been both the head of government of Presidency of Cristina Fernández de Kirchner and also the director of Breaking Bad?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_125", "question": "Who has been both the head of government of Sixteenth government of Israel and also the director of The Great Dictator?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_126", "question": "Who has been both the head of government of Kan Cabinet and also the director of Solaris?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_127", "question": "Who has been both the head of government of Kan Cabinet (First Reshuffle) and also the director of 8½?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_128", "question": "Who has been both the head of government of Cabinet of Ivo Sanader I and also the director of Variety Lights?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_129", "question": "Who has been both the head of government of Government of the 3rd Scottish Parliament and also the director of A Clockwork Orange?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_130", "question": "Who has been both the head of government of Ottoman Bosnia and Herzegovina and also the director of The Shining?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_131", "question": "Who has been both the head of government of Blair governments and also the director of La Strada?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_132", "question": "Who has been both the head of government of François Bonneau and also the director of Il bidone?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_133", "question": "Who has been both the head of government of Flensburg Government and also the director of Nights of Cabiria?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_134", "question": "Who has been both the head of government of Russian Provisional Government and also the director of The Sacrifice?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_135", "question": "Who has been both the head of government of Bahrain and also the director of Burlesque on Carmen?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_136", "question": "Who has been both the head of government of Kan Cabinet (Second Reshuffle) and also the director of 2001: A Space Odyssey?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_137", "question": "Who has been both the head of government of Cabinet of Ivo Sanader II and also the director of Eraserhead?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_138", "question": "Who has been both the head of government of Reinfeldt Cabinet and also the director of Eyes Wide Shut?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_139", "question": "Who has been both the head of government of thirty-sixth government of Israel and also the director of Full Metal Jacket?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_140", "question": "Who has been both the head of government of thirty-fifth government of Israel and also the director of Stalker?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_141", "question": "Who has been both the head of government of Second Yamamoto Cabinet and also the screenwriter of Wanted?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_142", "question": "Who has been both the head of government of Second Rudd Ministry and also the screenwriter of Kick-Ass?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_143", "question": "Who has been both the head of government of Second Manmohan Singh ministry and also the screenwriter of Twin Peaks?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_144", "question": "Who has been both the head of government of First Yamamoto Cabinet and also the screenwriter of Modern Times?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_145", "question": "Who has been both the head of government of thirty-fourth government of Israel and also the screenwriter of Hobbit?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_146", "question": "Who has been both the head of government of Ninth government of Israel and also the screenwriter of 2001: A Space Odyssey?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_147", "question": "Who has been both the head of government of Second Indira Gandhi Ministry and also the screenwriter of Eraserhead?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_148", "question": "Who has been both the head of government of Second Thatcher ministry and also the screenwriter of Solaris?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_149", "question": "Who has been both the head of government of Rajiv Gandhi Ministry and also the screenwriter of A Clockwork Orange?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_150", "question": "Who has been both the head of government of First Indira Gandhi Ministry and also the screenwriter of Breaking Bad?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_151", "question": "Who has been both the head of government of Third Indira Gandhi Ministry and also the screenwriter of The Shining?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_152", "question": "Who has been both the head of government of Third Merkel cabinet and also the screenwriter of The Hobbit: An Unexpected Journey?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_153", "question": "Who has been both the head of government of Galactic Republic and also the screenwriter of The Kid?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_154", "question": "Who has been both the head of government of Baiti District and also the screenwriter of The Lord of the Rings?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_155", "question": "Who has been both the head of government of Roman Catholic Diocese of Urgell and also the screenwriter of Macbeth?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_156", "question": "Who has been both the head of government of Noda Cabinet (Second Reshuffle) and also the screenwriter of Fun in Acapulco?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_157", "question": "Who has been both the head of government of Noda Cabinet and also the screenwriter of Falstaff?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_158", "question": "Who has been both the head of government of Stoltenberg's Second Cabinet and also the screenwriter of The Lord of the Rings: The Fellowship of the Ring?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_159", "question": "Who has been both the head of government of Hesham Qandil Ministry and also the screenwriter of The Gendarme and the Extra-Terrestrials?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_160", "question": "Who has been both the head of government of Eighth government of Israel and also the screenwriter of Full Metal Jacket?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_161", "question": "Who has been the head of government of Fifteenth government of Israel and also the composer of The Magic Flute?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_162", "question": "Who has been the head of government of First Hatta Cabinet and also the composer of Ascanio in Alba?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_163", "question": "Who has been the head of government of Fourteenth government of Israel and also the composer of Idomeneo?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_164", "question": "Who has been the head of government of Mera and also the composer of Eine kleine Nachtmusik?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_165", "question": "Who has been the head of government of Fourth government of Israel and also the composer of Mitridate, re di Ponto?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_166", "question": "Who has been the head of government of First Manmohan Singh ministry and also the composer of Don Juan, or If Don Juan Were a Woman?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_167", "question": "Who has been the head of government of Meneng District and also the composer of Fata Morgana?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_168", "question": "Who has been the head of government of Fourth Merkel cabinet and also the composer of La finta giardiniera?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_169", "question": "Who has been the head of government of Fourth Nehru ministry and also the composer of Bastien und Bastienne?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_170", "question": "Who has been the head of government of Third Nehru ministry and also the composer of Nikita?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_171", "question": "Who has been the head of government of Monti Cabinet and also the composer of The Magic Flute?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_172", "question": "Who has been the head of government of Schillingen and also the composer of Piano Sonata No. 10?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_173", "question": "Who has been the head of government of Venezuela and also the composer of String Quartet No. 14?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_174", "question": "Who has been the head of government of Wojciech Grochowski and also the composer of Flute Quartet No. 1?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_175", "question": "Who has been the head of government of Japan and also the composer of String Quartet No. 1?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_176", "question": "Who has been the head of government of Mecklenburg-Western Pomerania and also the composer of String Quintet No. 6?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_177", "question": "Who has been the head of government of Saxony-Anhalt and also the composer of Piano Quartet No. 1?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_178", "question": "Who has been the head of government of London and also the composer of Prussian Quartets?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_179", "question": "Who has been the head of government of Connecticut and also the composer of Amadeus?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_180", "question": "Who has been the head of government of First Thatcher ministry and also the composer of Piano Sonata No. 11?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_181", "question": "Who has been the head of government of Government of National Unity and also serves as the editor for Grimms' fairy tales?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_182", "question": "Who has been the head of government of Dominion of Ghana and also serves as the editor for Die Rote Fahne?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_183", "question": "Who has been the head of government of Council of People's Commissars and also serves as the editor for Course in General Linguistics?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_184", "question": "Who has been the head of government of Churchill war ministry and also serves as the editor for United States Reports?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_185", "question": "Who has been the head of government of First Cabinet of Independent India and also serves as the editor for Rheinische Zeitung?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_186", "question": "Who has been the head of government of Friesland and also serves as the editor for Sovremennik?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_187", "question": "Who has been the head of government of Rhineland-Palatinate and also serves as the editor for Siege of Rhodes?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_188", "question": "Who has been the head of government of Verona and also serves as the editor for Encarta?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_189", "question": "Who has been the head of government of Second Modi ministry and also serves as the editor for Iskra?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_190", "question": "Who has been the head of government of Third Cabinet of Donald Tusk and also serves as the editor for The Metamorphosis?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_191", "question": "Who has been the head of government of Australia and also serves as the editor for Logical Methods in Computer Science?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_192", "question": "Who has been the head of government of Birkenheide and also serves as the editor for La arto labori kune : festlibro por Humphrey Tonkin?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_193", "question": "Who has been the head of government of Czechoslovakia and also serves as the editor for Book of Documents?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_194", "question": "Who has been the head of government of Leer and also serves as the editor for Notebook for Anna Magdalena Bach?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_195", "question": "Who has been the head of government of Charente-Maritime and also serves as the editor for Household Words?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_196", "question": "Who has been the head of government of Ulm and also serves as the editor for DB Welt?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_197", "question": "Who has been the head of government of Baden-Württemberg and also serves as the editor for Znanie?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_198", "question": "Who has been the head of government of Saint Petersburg and also serves as the editor for Toledan Tables?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_199", "question": "Who has been the head of government of Antwerp and also serves as the editor for Who's Who of American Returned Students?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_200", "question": "Who has been the head of government of Province of Liege and also serves as the editor for Who's Who of American Returned Students?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_201", "question": "Who has been the head of government of Third Lee Hsien Loong Cabinet and also the employer of Albert Einstein?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_202", "question": "Who has been the head of government of Twenty-first government of Israel and also the employer of Max Levchin?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_203", "question": "Who has been the head of government of 60th Cabinet of Thailand and also the employer of Joshua Bloch?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_204", "question": "Who has been the head of government of Prime Minister's Office and also the employer of Willy Brandt?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_205", "question": "Who has been the head of government of Second Lee Hsien Loong Cabinet and also the employer of Thomas Pynchon?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_206", "question": "Who has been the head of government of Juncker-Polfer Ministry and also the employer of Gonzalo Jiménez de Quesada?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_207", "question": "Who has been the head of government of thirty-seventh government of Israel and also the employer of Ed H. Chi?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_208", "question": "Who has been the head of government of Israeli war cabinet and also the employer of Emmanuel Mogenet?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_209", "question": "Who has been the head of government of Jyrki Katainen's cabinet and also the employer of Raymond Kurzweil?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_210", "question": "Who has been the head of government of Second Azarov Government and also the employer of Thomas Bushnell?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_211", "question": "Who has been the head of government of XIX Constitutional Government of Portugal and also the employer of Susan Landau?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_212", "question": "Who has been the head of government of Churchill caretaker ministry and also the employer of Marissa Mayer?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_213", "question": "Who has been the head of government of Third Thatcher ministry and also the employer of Hoodie Allen?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_214", "question": "Who has been the head of government of Second Nehru ministry and also the employer of Rob Pike?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_215", "question": "Who has been the head of government of Third Churchill ministry and also the employer of Andy Hertzfeld?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_216", "question": "Who has been the head of government of First Modi ministry and also the employer of Jacob L. Moreno?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_217", "question": "Who has been the head of government of Second Cameron ministry and also the employer of Max Margules?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_218", "question": "Who has been the head of government of Estonian Soviet Socialist Republic and also the employer of Jeff Dean?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_219", "question": "Who has been the head of government of Weißwasser and also the employer of Jill Hazelbaker?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_220", "question": "Who has been the head of government of Indonesia and also the employer of Ben Laurie?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_221", "question": "Who has been the head of government of German South-West Africa and also the founder of Google+?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_222", "question": "Who has been the head of government of Yang Wending and also the founder of United Nations?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_223", "question": "Who has been the head of government of Democratic Government of Albania and also the founder of Wikipedia?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_224", "question": "Who has been the head of government of First Order and also the founder of WikiLeaks?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_225", "question": "Who has been the head of government of Kazan and also the founder of Solidarity?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_226", "question": "Who has been the head of government of Neckar-Odenwald and also the founder of European Union?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_227", "question": "Who has been the head of government of Worms and also the founder of Wikibooks?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_228", "question": "Who has been the head of government of Cabinet of Antonis Samaras and also the founder of Wiktionary?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_229", "question": "Who has been the head of government of Juncker-Asselborn Ministry I and also the founder of Wikimedia Commons?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_230", "question": "Who has been the head of government of Noda Cabinet (First Reshuffle) and also the founder of Wikiquote?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_231", "question": "Who has been the head of government of first Kenny ministry and also the founder of Mercosur?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_232", "question": "Who has been the head of government of Stoltenberg's First Cabinet and also the founder of Wikimedia Foundation?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_233", "question": "Who has been the head of government of Noda Cabinet (Third Reshuffle) and also the founder of Nederlandse Spoorwegen?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_234", "question": "Who has been the head of government of Osaka Prefecture and also the founder of Pittsburgh?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_235", "question": "Who has been the head of government of Vladivostok and also the founder of Wikinews?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_236", "question": "Who has been the head of government of Trentino-South Tyrol and also the founder of Christianity?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_237", "question": "Who has been the head of government of Bergamo and also the founder of Arab League?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_238", "question": "Who has been the head of government of Iraq and also the founder of Legion of Honour?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_239", "question": "Who has been the head of government of Saxony and also the founder of World Wide Web Consortium?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_240", "question": "Who has been the head of government of Toronto and also the founder of Bloomberg L.P.?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_241", "question": "Who has been the head of government of Ghent and also the cast member in Bowling for Columbine?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_242", "question": "Who has been the head of government of Orange and also the cast member in Live Free or Die Hard?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_243", "question": "Who has been the head of government of Mutasarrifate of Jerusalem and also the cast member in How I Met Your Mother?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_244", "question": "Who has been the head of government of Calabria and also the cast member in The Good Wife?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_245", "question": "Who has been the head of government of Veenendaal and also the cast member in Swing Vote?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_246", "question": "Who has been the head of government of Münster and also the cast member in Triumph of the Will?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_247", "question": "Who has been the head of government of Abu Dhabi and also the cast member in Olympia?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_248", "question": "Who has been the head of government of Bremerhaven and also the cast member in Last Days of Mussolini?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_249", "question": "Who has been the head of government of Fourth Rutte cabinet and also the cast member in Lemony Snicket's A Series of Unfortunate Events?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_250", "question": "Who has been the head of government of Fourth cabinet of Viktor Orbán and also the cast member in The Manchurian Candidate?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_251", "question": "Who has been the head of government of Liguria and also the cast member in Zelig?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_252", "question": "Who has been the head of government of Andernach and also the cast member in Prisoner of Paradise?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_253", "question": "Who has been the head of government of New Mexico and also the cast member in The Eternal Jew?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_254", "question": "Who has been the head of government of Emirate of Umm Al Quwain and also the cast member in The Deer Hunter?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_255", "question": "Who has been the head of government of Abruzzo and also the cast member in Kramer vs. Kramer?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_256", "question": "Who has been the head of government of Bregenz and also the cast member in The Assassination of Richard Nixon?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_257", "question": "Who has been the head of government of Quimper and also the cast member in 11'09\"01 September 11?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_258", "question": "Who has been the head of government of Friuli Venezia Giulia and also the cast member in I Am Twenty?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_259", "question": "Who has been the head of government of Ventspils and also the cast member in Tickle Me?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_260", "question": "Who has been the head of government of Meaux and also the cast member in Jailhouse Rock?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_261", "question": "Who has been the head of government of Czech National Council and also the sibling of Elagabalus?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_262", "question": "Who has been the head of government of Yukon and also the sibling of Titus?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_263", "question": "Who has been the head of government of Martínez and also the sibling of Ptolemy IX Lathyros?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_264", "question": "Who has been the head of government of Denigomodu District and also the sibling of Ptolemy X Alexander I?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_265", "question": "Who has been the head of government of Communauté d'agglomération du Pays de Meaux and also the sibling of Joseph Bonaparte?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_266", "question": "Who has been the head of government of third cabinet of Jean-Pierre Raffarin and also the sibling of Alois Hitler, Jr.?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_267", "question": "Who has been the head of government of Gries am Brenner and also the sibling of Eleanor of Castile?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_268", "question": "Who has been the head of government of Republic of Artsakh and also the sibling of James the Just?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_269", "question": "Who has been the head of government of Shidehara Cabinet and also the sibling of Ptolemy VI?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_270", "question": "Who has been the head of government of Alpes-Maritimes and also the sibling of Domitian?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_271", "question": "Who has been the head of government of XX Constitutional Government of Portugal and also the sibling of Cleopatra IV of Egypt?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_272", "question": "Who has been the head of government of Twenty-sixth government of Israel and also the sibling of Charles I of Naples?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_273", "question": "Who has been the head of government of Third Rutte cabinet and also the sibling of Elisa Bonaparte?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_274", "question": "Who has been the head of government of Bergisch Gladbach and also the sibling of Berenice IV of Egypt?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_275", "question": "Who has been the head of government of Basque Autonomous Community and also the sibling of Paula Hitler?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_276", "question": "Who has been the head of government of Schleswig and also the sibling of Maria Anna Mozart?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_277", "question": "Who has been the head of government of Federal Ministry of Health of Germany and also the sibling of Louis Bonaparte?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_278", "question": "Who has been the head of government of Greiz and also the sibling of Antiochus IV Epiphanes?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_279", "question": "Who has been the head of government of Sächsische Schweiz-Osterzgebirge and also the sibling of Pauline Bonaparte?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_280", "question": "Who has been the head of government of Erfurt District and also the sibling of Seleucus III Ceraunus?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_281", "question": "Who is the sibling of Baudouin I of Belgium and also the father of Commodus?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_282", "question": "Who is the sibling of Pamela Springsteen and also the father of Caracalla?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_283", "question": "Who is the sibling of Bakr bin Laden and also the father of Napoleon II?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_284", "question": "Who is the sibling of Nero Caesar and also the father of Seti I?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_285", "question": "Who is the sibling of Severus Alexander and also the father of Tiberius?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_286", "question": "Who is the sibling of Germanicus and also the father of Titus?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_287", "question": "Who is the sibling of Geta and also the father of Nero?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_288", "question": "Who is the sibling of Tecumseh and also the father of Caesarion?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_289", "question": "Who is the sibling of Quintus Tullius Cicero and also the father of Johann Christoph Friedrich Bach?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_290", "question": "Who is the sibling of Lucius Cornelius Scipio Asiaticus and also the father of Princess Januária, Countess of Aquila?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_291", "question": "Who is the sibling of Seishi Kishimoto and also the father of Princess Maria Amélia of Brazil?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_292", "question": "Who is the sibling of Agrippina the Younger and also the father of Princess Francisca of Brazil?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_293", "question": "Who is the sibling of Infanta Isabel Maria of Portugal and also the father of Christopher Tolkien?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_294", "question": "Who is the sibling of Infanta Maria Francisca of Portugal and also the father of Ögedei Khan?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_295", "question": "Who is the sibling of Queen Maria Isabel of Spain and also the father of Jochi?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_296", "question": "Who is the sibling of Angela Hitler and also the father of Cedella Marley?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_297", "question": "Who is the sibling of Ramesses VIII and also the father of Lisa Marie Presley?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_298", "question": "Who is the sibling of Ramesses VI and also the father of Agnes of France, Duchess of Burgundy?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_299", "question": "Who is the sibling of Lucilla and also the father of Johann Christian Bach?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_300", "question": "Who is the sibling of Berengaria of Castile and also the father of Wilhelm Friedemann Bach?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_301", "question": "Who is the sibling of Jeb Bush and also the mother of Hephaestus?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_302", "question": "Who is the sibling of Ptolemy XIV of Egypt and also the mother of Esha Deol?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_303", "question": "Who is the sibling of Jacques-Joseph Champollion and also the mother of Arsinoe II?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_304", "question": "Who is the sibling of Robert I, Count of Artois and also the mother of Cleopatra Selene of Egypt and Syria?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_305", "question": "Who is the sibling of Arsinoe IV of Egypt and also the mother of Irène Joliot-Curie?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_306", "question": "Who is the sibling of Ptolemy XIII Theos Philopator and also the mother of Albert II, Prince of Monaco?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_307", "question": "Who is the sibling of Abel Hugo and also the mother of Elizabeth II?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_308", "question": "Who is the sibling of Miguel I of Portugal and also the mother of Gwyneth Paltrow?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_309", "question": "Who is the sibling of Octavia the Younger and also the mother of Rajiv Gandhi?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_310", "question": "Who is the sibling of Ulpia Marciana and also the mother of Caesarion?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_311", "question": "Who is the sibling of Livilla and also the mother of James the Just?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_312", "question": "Who is the sibling of Isabelle of France and also the mother of Cleopatra II of Egypt?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_313", "question": "Who is the sibling of Urraca of Castile and also the mother of Ptolemy II Philadelphus?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_314", "question": "Who is the sibling of Neil Bush and also the mother of Hastings Russell, 12th Duke of Bedford?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_315", "question": "Who is the sibling of Titus Flavius Sabinus and also the mother of Jessica Capshaw?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_316", "question": "Who is the sibling of Antiochus III the Great and also the mother of Princess Astrid, Archduchess of Austria-Este?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_317", "question": "Who is the sibling of Seleucus IV Philopator and also the mother of Khonsu?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_318", "question": "Who is the sibling of Cleopatra II of Egypt and also the mother of Michael V Kalaphates?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_319", "question": "Who is the sibling of Cleopatra Selene of Egypt and Syria and also the mother of Louis IX of France?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_320", "question": "Who is the sibling of Itachi Uchiha and also the mother of Victor Amadeus II of Savoy?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_321", "question": "Who is the sibling of Drusus Caesar and also the spouse of Joseph?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_322", "question": "Who is the sibling of Nero Claudius Drusus and also the spouse of Veronica Carstens?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_323", "question": "Who is the sibling of Kartikeya and also the spouse of Anna Magdalena Bach?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_324", "question": "Who is the sibling of Jose Cojuangco, Jr. and also the spouse of Maria Barbara Bach?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_325", "question": "Who is the sibling of Maecia Faustina and also the spouse of Bettina Wulff?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_326", "question": "Who is the sibling of Bronisław Piłsudski and also the spouse of Cleopatra Selene of Egypt and Syria?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_327", "question": "Who is the sibling of Martin Ohm and also the spouse of Cleopatra IV of Egypt?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_328", "question": "Who is the sibling of Kris Aquino and also the spouse of Cleopatra III of Egypt?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_329", "question": "Who is the sibling of Amun-her-khepeshef and also the spouse of Mildred Harris?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_330", "question": "Who is the sibling of Caroline Bonaparte and also the spouse of Joachim Sauer?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_331", "question": "Who is the sibling of Lucien Bonaparte and also the spouse of Elsa Einstein?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_332", "question": "Who is the sibling of Dorothy Bush Koch and also the spouse of Lita Grey?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_333", "question": "Who is the sibling of Olivier Sarkozy and also the spouse of Nadezhda Alliluyeva?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_334", "question": "Who is the sibling of Julia Livilla and also the spouse of Pompeia?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_335", "question": "Who is the sibling of Julia Drusilla and also the spouse of Benigno Aquino Jr.?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_336", "question": "Who is the sibling of Julia Minor and also the spouse of Julia Domna?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_337", "question": "Who is the sibling of Adeimantus of Collytus and also the spouse of Demi Moore?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_338", "question": "Who is the sibling of Vijaya Lakshmi Pandit and also the spouse of Mark Antony?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_339", "question": "Who is the sibling of Jackie Jackson and also the spouse of Sean Penn?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_340", "question": "Who is the sibling of Jarosław Kaczyński and also the spouse of Marcus Vipsanius Agrippa?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_341", "question": "Who is the sibling of Jérôme Bonaparte and also has been the head of state of Belarus?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_342", "question": "Who is the sibling of Marvin P. Bush and also has been the head of state of Croatia?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_343", "question": "Who is the sibling of Henry I of Castile and also has been the head of state of Monaco?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_344", "question": "Who is the sibling of Alphonse, Count of Poitiers and also has been the head of state of Luxembourg?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_345", "question": "Who is the sibling of Salome and also has been the head of state of Kazakhstan?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_346", "question": "Who is the sibling of Mary of Clopas and also has been the head of state of Andorra?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_347", "question": "Who is the sibling of Cleopatra I Syra and also has been the head of state of Togo?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_348", "question": "Who is the sibling of Georg Ratzinger and also has been the head of state of German Democratic Republic?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_349", "question": "Who is the sibling of Princess Viktoria of Prussia and also has been the head of state of Tenochtitlan?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_350", "question": "Who is the sibling of Princess Margaret of Prussia and also has been the head of state of United Arab Emirates?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_351", "question": "Who is the sibling of Maria Ulyanova and also has been the head of state of German Empire?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_352", "question": "Who is the sibling of Anna Ulyanova and also has been the head of state of Turkey?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_353", "question": "Who is the sibling of Salem bin Laden and also has been the head of state of Alberta?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_354", "question": "Who is the sibling of Annia Cornificia Faustina and also has been the head of state of People's Republic of China?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_355", "question": "Who is the sibling of Lucius Vitellius and also has been the head of state of Azerbaijan?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_356", "question": "Who is the sibling of Aleksandr Ulyanov and also has been the head of state of Uzbekistan?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_357", "question": "Who is the sibling of Åke Hammarskjöld and also has been the head of state of Aruba?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_358", "question": "Who is the sibling of Tarek bin Laden and also has been the head of state of People's Republic of Bulgaria?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_359", "question": "Who is the sibling of Auma Obama and also has been the head of state of Curaçao?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_360", "question": "Who is the sibling of Henutmire and also has been the head of state of Liberia?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_361", "question": "Who is the sibling of Lucius Junius Gallio Annaeanus and also the child of Augustus?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_362", "question": "Who is the sibling of Jim Hanks and also the child of Mary Lee Woods?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_363", "question": "Who is the sibling of Pentawer and also the child of Rhea Silvia?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_364", "question": "Who is the sibling of Carl Friedrich von Weizsäcker and also the child of Scribonia?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_365", "question": "Who is the sibling of Yuka Murofushi and also the child of Eduardo Frei Montalva?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_366", "question": "Who is the sibling of Princess Charlotte of Prussia and also the child of Blanche of Castile?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_367", "question": "Who is the sibling of Prince Henry of Prussia and also the child of Federico Errázuriz Zañartu?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_368", "question": "Who is the sibling of Hugh and also the child of Manuel Montt?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_369", "question": "Who is the sibling of Constanza de Castilla and also the child of Seneca the Elder?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_370", "question": "Who is the sibling of Carloman I and also the child of Katherine Jackson?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_371", "question": "Who is the sibling of Princess Stéphanie of Monaco and also the child of Alois Hitler?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_372", "question": "Who is the sibling of Sarah Lincoln Grigsby and also the child of Carlo Bonaparte?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_373", "question": "Who is the sibling of Gilbert Shakespeare and also the child of Maria-Letizia Bonaparte?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_374", "question": "Who is the sibling of Erasmus Alvey Darwin and also the child of Antoninus Pius?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_375", "question": "Who is the sibling of Maria Teresa de Bragança and also the child of Hoelun?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_376", "question": "Who is the sibling of Thomas Corneille and also the child of Ser Piero da Vinci?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_377", "question": "Who is the sibling of Tryphaena and also the child of Yesugei?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_378", "question": "Who is the sibling of Infanta Ana de Jesus Maria, Marchioness of Loulé and also the child of Mary Shakespeare?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_379", "question": "Who is the sibling of Princess Joséphine-Charlotte of Belgium and also the child of Minato Namikaze?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_380", "question": "Who is the sibling of Sophia of Prussia and also the child of João VI of Portugal?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_381", "question": "Who is the sibling of Thierry Séchan and also the director in Pay Day?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_382", "question": "Who is the sibling of Paddy Bush and also the director in Fellini: A Director's Notebook?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_383", "question": "Who is the sibling of Norah Borges and also the director in The Clowns?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_384", "question": "Who is the sibling of Sydney Chaplin and also the director in Roma?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_385", "question": "Who is the sibling of Qasar and also the director in Band of Brothers?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_386", "question": "Who is the sibling of Belgutei and also the director in Kill Bill: The Whole Bloody Affair?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_387", "question": "Who is the sibling of Behter and also the director in Getting Acquainted?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_388", "question": "Who is the sibling of Hachiun and also the director in Andrei Rublev?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_389", "question": "Who is the sibling of Temüge and also the director in La Dolce Vita?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_390", "question": "Who is the sibling of Janet Jackson and also the director in Pretty Little Liars?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_391", "question": "Who is the sibling of Princess Marie-Christine of Belgium and also the director in Reservoir Dogs?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_392", "question": "Who is the sibling of Grimoald the Younger and also the director in The Lord of the Rings: The Fellowship of the Ring?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_393", "question": "Who is the sibling of Mike McGear and also the director in The Gold Rush?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_394", "question": "Who is the sibling of Antiochus Hierax and also the director in City Lights?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_395", "question": "Who is the sibling of Bo Hammarskjöld and also the director in The Lord of the Rings trilogy?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_396", "question": "Who is the sibling of Ceionia Plautia and also the director in The Hobbit: An Unexpected Journey?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_397", "question": "Who is the sibling of Enriqueta Pinto Garmendia and also the director in Stardust?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_398", "question": "Who is the sibling of Olga Ulyanova and also the director in X-Men: First Class?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_399", "question": "Who is the sibling of Cornelia and also the director in King Kong?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_400", "question": "Who is the sibling of Marie-Agnès de Gaulle and also the director in The Lord of the Rings: The Return of the King?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_401", "question": "Who is the sibling of Raditz and also the editor for God Created the Integers?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_402", "question": "Who is the sibling of Randy Jackson and also the editor for The I.V. Stalin White Sea – Baltic Sea Canal?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_403", "question": "Who is the sibling of Tito Jackson and also the editor for Geunsa-rok?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_404", "question": "Who is the sibling of Julia Major and also the editor for Vox?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_405", "question": "Who is the sibling of Julia Baird and also the editor for Paper Mario: The Origami King?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_406", "question": "Who is the sibling of Marlon Jackson and also the editor for Bibliography of Xuanhe calligraphy?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_407", "question": "Who is the sibling of Jermaine Jackson and also the editor for Astronomiae Instauratae Progymnasmata?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_408", "question": "Who is the sibling of Christopher Ciccone and also the editor for The International Pharmacopoeia?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_409", "question": "Who is the sibling of Hilary Arthur Reuel Tolkien and also the editor for Xuanhe Huapu?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_410", "question": "Who is the sibling of La Toya Jackson and also the editor for Nintendo Direct?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_411", "question": "Who is the sibling of Kaspar Anton Karl van Beethoven and also the editor for Allgemeine Encyclopädie der Wissenschaften und Künste?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_412", "question": "Who is the sibling of Eric Hernandez and also the editor for Black Mask?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_413", "question": "Who is the sibling of Susan Adams and also the editor for Acta Mathematica Sinica?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_414", "question": "Who is the sibling of Rebbie Jackson and also the editor for A Writer's Diary?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_415", "question": "Who is the sibling of Caroline, Princess of Hanover and also the editor for Encyclopédie nouvelle?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_416", "question": "Who is the sibling of Johann Christoph Bach III and also the editor for Gardiner's sign list?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_417", "question": "Who is the sibling of Dmitry Ulyanov and also the editor for The Daily Beast?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_418", "question": "Who is the sibling of Edmund Shakespeare and also the editor for The Cambridge Ancient History?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_419", "question": "Who is the sibling of Maya Soetoro-Ng and also the editor for Weird Tales?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_420", "question": "Who is the sibling of Min Aung Hlaing and also the editor for Thieme-Becker-Vollmer?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_421", "question": "Who is the sibling of Leon Amundsen and also the employer of Dick Costolo?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_422", "question": "Who is the sibling of Infanta Maria da Assunção of Portugal and also the employer of Kellee Santiago?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_423", "question": "Who is the sibling of Glaucon and also the employer of Matt Cutts?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_424", "question": "Who is the sibling of Joan Shakespeare and also the employer of Rexford Tugwell?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_425", "question": "Who is the sibling of Temulin and also the employer of Johann Böhm?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_426", "question": "Who is the sibling of Christoph Harting and also the employer of Christopher Ferguson?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_427", "question": "Who is the sibling of Laodice III and also the employer of Ben Jai?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_428", "question": "Who is the sibling of Ceres and also the employer of Alan Eustace?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_429", "question": "Who is the sibling of Trace Cyrus and also the employer of Hartmut Mehdorn?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_430", "question": "Who is the sibling of James Franklin and also the employer of Jawed Karim?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_431", "question": "Who is the sibling of Lucius Salvius Otho Titianus and also the employer of David Korn?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_432", "question": "Who is the sibling of Neptune and also the employer of Franz Josef Och?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_433", "question": "Who is the sibling of Burna Boy and also the employer of Mike Harrington?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_434", "question": "Who is the sibling of Malik Obama and also the employer of Hal Varian?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_435", "question": "Who is the sibling of Jupiter and also the employer of Theodore Ts'o?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_436", "question": "Who is the sibling of Gisela, Abbess of Chelles and also the employer of Andrew Morton?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_437", "question": "Who is the sibling of Childebrand I and also the employer of Corinna Cortes?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_438", "question": "Who is the sibling of Ptolemy Apion and also the employer of Peter J. Weinberger?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_439", "question": "Who is the sibling of Laodice and also the employer of Stuart Feldman?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_440", "question": "Who is the sibling of Drogo of Champagne and also the employer of David Weinberger?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_441", "question": "Who is the sibling of Princess Marie-Esméralda, Lady Moncada and also the founder of Wikidata?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_442", "question": "Who is the sibling of Emperor Wenzong of Tang and also the founder of École Centrale de Lille?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_443", "question": "Who is the sibling of Antiochus and also the founder of Federation Cynologique Internationale?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_444", "question": "Who is the sibling of Marcus Kasner and also the founder of École nationale vétérinaire d'Alfort?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_445", "question": "Who is the sibling of Irene Kasner and also the founder of Gallerie dell'Accademia?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_446", "question": "Who is the sibling of Meinhard Schwarzenegger and also the founder of Benelux?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_447", "question": "Who is the sibling of Mark Okoth Obama Ndesandjo and also the founder of Televisión Nacional de Chile?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_448", "question": "Who is the sibling of José Elías Balmaceda and also the founder of Andean Community?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_449", "question": "Who is the sibling of Margot Frank and also the founder of ASEAN?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_450", "question": "Who is the sibling of Anne Hamilton and also the founder of European Space Agency?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_451", "question": "Who is the sibling of John Hamilton and also the founder of Wikispecies?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_452", "question": "Who is the sibling of Tiara Hernandez and also the founder of Louvre Museum?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_453", "question": "Who is the sibling of Tahiti Hernandez and also the founder of Azienda Trasporti Milanesi?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_454", "question": "Who is the sibling of Jaime Kailani and also the founder of Pasteur Institute?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_455", "question": "Who is the sibling of Juander Santos and also the founder of Royal Museums of Fine Arts of Belgium?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_456", "question": "Who is the sibling of Noah Cyrus and also the founder of Scuola Normale Superiore?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_457", "question": "Who is the sibling of Michael Jackson and also the founder of Alliance française?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_458", "question": "Who is the sibling of Anne Shakespeare and also the founder of Fandom?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_459", "question": "Who is the sibling of Richard Shakespeare and also the founder of Yle?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_460", "question": "Who is the sibling of Margaret Shakespeare and also the founder of Continental Army?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_461", "question": "Who is the sibling of Joan Shakespeare and also the cast member in Harum Scarum?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_462", "question": "Who is the sibling of Prince Waldemar of Prussia and also the cast member in A Bridge Too Far?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_463", "question": "Who is the sibling of Laodice IV and also the cast member in Girl Happy?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_464", "question": "Who is the sibling of Prince Sigismund of Prussia and also the cast member in Tag der Freiheit: Unsere Wehrmacht?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_465", "question": "Who is the sibling of Prince Alexandre of Belgium and also the cast member in Truth in Numbers? Everything, According to Wikipedia?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_466", "question": "Who is the sibling of Otto Hitler and also the cast member in JAG?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_467", "question": "Who is the sibling of Napoleon and also the cast member in The Hours?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_468", "question": "Who is the sibling of Juno and also the cast member in The Adjustment Bureau?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_469", "question": "Who is the sibling of Charles X of France and also the cast member in The Ides of March?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_470", "question": "Who is the sibling of Lisa Simpson and also the cast member in EDtv?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_471", "question": "Who is the sibling of Ayra Starr and also the cast member in The House of the Spirits?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_472", "question": "Who is the sibling of Alexander Jagiellon and also the cast member in Adaptation?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_473", "question": "Who is the sibling of Liam Hemsworth and also the cast member in Hope Springs?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_474", "question": "Who is the sibling of Lothar von Richthofen and also the cast member in Green Zone?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_475", "question": "Who is the sibling of Ramesses IV and also the cast member in Fahrenheit 9/11?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_476", "question": "Who is the sibling of Emperor Muzong of Tang and also the cast member in The War on Democracy?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_477", "question": "Who is the sibling of Emperor Jingzong of Tang and also the cast member in Anne Frank: The Whole Story?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_478", "question": "Who is the sibling of James Hamilton, 3rd Earl of Arran and also the cast member in Germany, Year Zero?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_479", "question": "Who is the sibling of Louis XVIII of France and also the cast member in Chaplin?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_480", "question": "Who is the sibling of Princess Yichang and also the cast member in Law & Order?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_481", "question": "Who is the sibling of Li Yi and also has received the award for Paris?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_482", "question": "Who is the sibling of Li Shi and also has received the award for asteroid?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_483", "question": "Who is the sibling of Li Shi and also has received the award for 4?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_484", "question": "Who is the sibling of Princess Taihe and also has received the award for Maria Moors Cabot Prizes?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_485", "question": "Who is the sibling of Bart Simpson and also has received the award for Hawthornden Prize?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_486", "question": "Who is the sibling of Nikita Mikhalkov and also has received the award for 5?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_487", "question": "Who is the sibling of Pluto and also has received the award for Saturn Award for Best Special Effects?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_488", "question": "Who is the sibling of Li Shi and also has received the award for 1980 Summer Olympics?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_489", "question": "Who is the sibling of Li Shi and also has received the award for 2012 Summer Olympics?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_490", "question": "Who is the sibling of Li Mou and also has received the award for Eurovision Song Contest?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_491", "question": "Who is the sibling of Li Shi and also has received the award for Figueres?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_492", "question": "Who is the sibling of Princess Gui and also has received the award for sport?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_493", "question": "Who is the sibling of Li Shi and also has received the award for Pisces?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_494", "question": "Who is the sibling of Princess Shaoyang and also has received the award for Academy Award for Technical Achievement?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_495", "question": "Who is the sibling of Prince Leopold of Bavaria and also has received the award for Academy Scientific and Technical Award?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_496", "question": "Who is the sibling of Amalie Auguste of Bavaria and also has received the award for kiss?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_497", "question": "Who is the sibling of Andrei Konchalovsky and also has received the award for The New York Times?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_498", "question": "Who is the sibling of Miley Cyrus and also has received the award for Nobel Prize?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_499", "question": "Where was Dale Frail born and also the place where Masabumi Hosono passed away?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_500", "question": "Where was Makyla Smith born and also the place where Hayashizaki Shigenobu passed away?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_501", "question": "Where was Peter Scheerer born and also the place where Ryogo Kubo passed away?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_502", "question": "Where was Herb Sutter born and also the place where Keizan passed away?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_503", "question": "Where was Avi Lewis born and also the place where Akatsuki Kambayashi passed away?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_504", "question": "Where was Benjamin Lumley born and also the place where Kōshō Uchiyama passed away?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_505", "question": "Where was Rob Pike born and also the place where Lucius Clodius Macer passed away?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_506", "question": "Where was Elza Kephart born and also the place where Hiroshi Kanazawa passed away?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_507", "question": "Where was Terri Tatchell born and also the place where Jiro Yoshihara passed away?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_508", "question": "Where was Wendy McElroy born and also the place where Afonso de Paiva passed away?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_509", "question": "Where was Christian Tessier born and also the place where Masaru Emoto passed away?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_510", "question": "Where was Jennifer Howell born and also the place where Zeami Motokiyo passed away?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_511", "question": "Where was Barbie Wilde born and also the place where Genichi Taguchi passed away?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_512", "question": "Where was Daniel Goldberg born and also the place where Tatsumi Hijikata passed away?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_513", "question": "Where was Damian Lee born and also the place where Reizo Fukuhara passed away?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_514", "question": "Where was Demore Barnes born and also the place where Kazu Naoki passed away?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_515", "question": "Where was Stephen Williams born and also the place where Takashi Taniguchi passed away?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_516", "question": "Where was Kirk Shaw born and also the place where Misuzu Kaneko passed away?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_517", "question": "Where was Kelvin Kwan born and also the place where Emperor Kanmu passed away?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_518", "question": "Where was R. D. Reid born and also the place where Jisaburō Ozawa passed away?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_519", "question": "Where was James Masterson born and also the place where Ernesto Teodoro Moneta has been educated at?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_520", "question": "Where was Graeme Manson born and also the place where René Descartes has been educated at?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_521", "question": "Where was Andy Mikita born and also the place where Louis-Marie Aubert du Petit-Thouars has been educated at?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_522", "question": "Where was Basil H. Johnston born and also the place where Joseph Gallieni has been educated at?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_523", "question": "Where was Sheva Alomar born and also the place where Jan Żabiński has been educated at?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_524", "question": "Where was Serge Christiaenssens born and also the place where Achille Baraguey d'Hilliers has been educated at?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_525", "question": "Where was Jim McLarty born and also the place where Michel Virlogeux has been educated at?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_526", "question": "Where was Kate Vernon born and also the place where Jacques Massu has been educated at?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_527", "question": "Where was Moses the Black born and also the place where Théophile Corret de la Tour d'Auvergne has been educated at?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_528", "question": "Where was Rene Ohashi born and also the place where Charles Lanrezac has been educated at?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_529", "question": "Where was Martin Wood born and also the place where Ginger Rogers has been educated at?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_530", "question": "Where was Joyce Cheng born and also the place where Gabriel Voisin has been educated at?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_531", "question": "Where was John Draper born and also the place where Georges Catroux has been educated at?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_532", "question": "Where was Bre Blair born and also the place where Olivier de Germay has been educated at?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_533", "question": "Where was Michael Reed born and also the place where Sonia Delaunay has been educated at?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_534", "question": "Where was Daniel Petrie born and also the place where Nelly has been educated at?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_535", "question": "Where was David James Elliott born and also the place where Diego Rivera has been educated at?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_536", "question": "Where was Albert Lacombe born and also the place where Ewa Siemaszko has been educated at?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_537", "question": "Where was David Reale born and also the place where Jean-Claude Brialy has been educated at?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_538", "question": "Where was Charles S. Thompson born and also the place where Henri Gouraud has been educated at?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_539", "question": "Where was Tien Shinhan born and also the place where Graham Chapman was buried?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_540", "question": "Where was Gohan born and also the place where Stanisław Poniatowski was buried?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_541", "question": "Where was George McCowan born and also the place where Stanisław Ostrowski was buried?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_542", "question": "Where was Stephanie Savage born and also the place where John the Apostle was buried?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_543", "question": "Where was David Collier born and also the place where Princess Anna of Sweden was buried?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_544", "question": "Where was Fred Mandel born and also the place where Konrad I, Duke of Głogów was buried?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_545", "question": "Where was Robin Ward born and also the place where Konrad IV the Older was buried?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_546", "question": "Where was Roxanne McKee born and also the place where Konrad Laskonogi was buried?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_547", "question": "Where was Samantha McLeod born and also the place where Gertrude of Merania was buried?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_548", "question": "Where was Pierre Pettigrew born and also the place where Magnus Enckell was buried?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_549", "question": "Where was Lee Jae-yoon born and also the place where Joan, Princess of Portugal was buried?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_550", "question": "Where was Nicolas Wright born and also the place where Cynane was buried?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_551", "question": "Where was Hillel Steiner born and also the place where Lambert of Maastricht was buried?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_552", "question": "Where was Hosea Ballou Morse born and also the place where Archduke Stefan of Austria was buried?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_553", "question": "Where was Dafna Linzer born and also the place where Luke the Evangelist was buried?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_554", "question": "Where was Adrian Alphona born and also the place where Anthony of Padua was buried?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_555", "question": "Where was Jeremy Guilbaut born and also the place where Mary de Bohun was buried?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_556", "question": "Where was Janne Mortil born and also the place where Toyotomi Hideyoshi was buried?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_557", "question": "Where was James Stewart born and also the place where James Murray, 2nd Duke of Atholl was buried?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_558", "question": "Where did Frederick C. Alderdice die and also the place where Louis-Gaston de Sonis has been educated at?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_559", "question": "Where did Emily Murphy die and also the place where James FitzJames, 1st Duke of Berwick has been educated at?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_560", "question": "Where did Yuthok Tashi Dhondup die and also the place where Aimable Pélissier has been educated at?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_561", "question": "Where did Ede Király die and also the place where Jean-Baptiste Budes, Comte de Guébriant has been educated at?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_562", "question": "Where did Janusz Brzozowski die and also the place where Jean Dussaulx has been educated at?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_563", "question": "Where did James M. Harrison die and also the place where Aristide Aubert du Petit-Thouars has been educated at?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_564", "question": "Where did Graham Leggat die and also the place where Odilon Barrot has been educated at?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_565", "question": "Where did Gordon Tanner die and also the place where François de Laval has been educated at?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_566", "question": "Where did Kiichiro Toyoda die and also the place where Louis d'Aurelle de Paladines has been educated at?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_567", "question": "Where did Hitoshi Imamura die and also the place where Patrick Baudry has been educated at?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_568", "question": "Where did Yozo Aoki die and also the place where Charles Denis Bourbaki has been educated at?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_569", "question": "Where did Shigeyoshi Suzuki die and also the place where Henri Gatien Bertrand has been educated at?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_570", "question": "Where did Gunichi Mikawa die and also the place where Rodolphe Belmer has been educated at?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_571", "question": "Where did Masao Ono die and also the place where Marin Mersenne has been educated at?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_572", "question": "Where did Go-Fukakusa-in no Nijō die and also the place where Paul Pau has been educated at?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_573", "question": "Where did Ichiji Otani die and also the place where Jean-François Clervoy has been educated at?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_574", "question": "Where did Namiki Sōsuke die and also the place where Marie Alphonse Bedeau has been educated at?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_575", "question": "Where did Yoshida Kenkō die and also the place where Louis Rossel has been educated at?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_576", "question": "Where did Kaoru Ishikawa die and also the place where François de La Rochefoucauld has been educated at?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_577", "question": "Where did Takeda Sōkaku die and also the place where Émile Lemoine has been educated at?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_578", "question": "Where did Motoo Kimura die and also the place where John Latham is buried?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_579", "question": "Where did Hōjō Masako die and also the place where Corey Haim is buried?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_580", "question": "Where did Kiyoo Kanda die and also the place where Dirk Hartog is buried?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_581", "question": "Where did Jiro Miyake die and also the place where Archduchess Catherine Renata of Austria is buried?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_582", "question": "Where did Tomoo Kudaka die and also the place where Nicholas Trivet is buried?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_583", "question": "Where did Himiko die and also the place where Karel Kuttelwascher is buried?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_584", "question": "Where did Kiyotake Kawaguchi die and also the place where Casimir I of Kuyavia is buried?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_585", "question": "Where did Toshiko Fujita die and also the place where Euphrosyne of Opole is buried?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_586", "question": "Where did Shunichi Kumai die and also the place where Joost van den Vondel is buried?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_587", "question": "Where did Tameo Ide die and also the place where Leopold II is buried?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_588", "question": "Where did Teiichi Matsumaru die and also the place where Tom Ketchum is buried?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_589", "question": "Where did Sam Carr die and also the place where Marcel Albert is buried?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_590", "question": "Where did Sébastien Rale die and also the place where Peter Zadek is buried?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_591", "question": "Where did Tom Thomson die and also the place where John Loudon McAdam is buried?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_592", "question": "Where did Rihei Sano die and also the place where Gorm the Old is buried?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_593", "question": "Where did Suh Sui Cho die and also the place where Roger of Wendover is buried?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_594", "question": "Where did Henry C. Gunning die and also the place where Ulrich von Wilamowitz-Moellendorff is buried?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_595", "question": "Where did Kenzo Ohashi die and also the place where Ronnie Peterson is buried?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_596", "question": "Where did Kanō Hōgai die and also the place where Enrico Caruso is buried?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_597", "question": "Where did Fukusaburo Harada die and also the place where Roger Keyes, 1st Baron Keyes is buried?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_598", "question": "Who is the father of Ramesses V and also the spouse of Jay Grdina?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_599", "question": "Who is the father of Gordian III and also the spouse of André Previn?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_600", "question": "Who is the father of Domitian and also the spouse of Yoko Ono?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_601", "question": "Who is the father of Marcus Aurelius and also the spouse of Empress Amélie of Brazil?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_602", "question": "Who is the father of Aníbal Pinto and also the spouse of Carrie Fisher?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_603", "question": "Who is the father of Federico Errázuriz Echaurren and also the spouse of Claudia Octavia?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_604", "question": "Who is the father of Hostilian and also the spouse of Poppaea Sabina?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_605", "question": "Who is the father of Diadumenian and also the spouse of Bruttia Crispina?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_606", "question": "Who is the father of Picus and also the spouse of Scribonia?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_607", "question": "Who is the father of Ziggy Marley and also the spouse of Faustina the Elder?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_608", "question": "Who is the father of Geraldine Chaplin and also the spouse of Agrippina the Younger?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_609", "question": "Who is the father of Philip III of France and also the spouse of Nefertari?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_610", "question": "Who is the father of Cupid and also the spouse of Emma Darwin?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_611", "question": "Who is the father of Romulus and Remus and also the spouse of Doris Schröder-Köpf?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_612", "question": "Who is the father of Jenna Bush Hager and also the spouse of Maria Leopoldina of Austria?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_613", "question": "Who is the father of Tad Lincoln and also the spouse of Maike Kohl-Richter?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_614", "question": "Who is the father of Severus Alexander and also the spouse of Margot Honecker?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_615", "question": "Who is the father of Antoninus Pius and also the spouse of Claudia Schiffer?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_616", "question": "Who is the father of Raghad Hussein and also the spouse of Augusta Victoria of Schleswig-Holstein?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_617", "question": "Who is the father of Julia and also the spouse of Amphitrite?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_618", "question": "Who is the father of Carl Linnaeus the Younger and also has been the head of state of Czechoslovakia?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_619", "question": "Who is the father of Chelsea Clinton and also has been the head of state of United Kingdom?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_620", "question": "Who is the father of Carl Philipp Emanuel Bach and also has been the head of state of East Francia?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_621", "question": "Who is the father of Hans Albert Einstein and also has been the head of state of Mongol Empire?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_622", "question": "Who is the father of Pedro II of Brazil and also has been the head of state of Sint Maarten?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_623", "question": "Who is the father of Bintanath and also has been the head of state of Bonaire?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_624", "question": "Who is the father of Jennifer Lynch and also has been the head of state of Quebec?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_625", "question": "Who is the father of Augustus and also has been the head of state of North German Confederation?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_626", "question": "Who is the father of Herennius Etruscus and also has been the head of state of Kingdom of Bulgaria?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_627", "question": "Who is the father of Merneptah and also has been the head of state of Austrian Empire?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_628", "question": "Who is the father of Tullia and also has been the head of state of Bahrain?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_629", "question": "Who is the father of Meritamen and also has been the head of state of Brazil?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_630", "question": "Who is the father of Nebettawy and also has been the head of state of Dutch colonial empire?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_631", "question": "Who is the father of Mazarine Pingeot and also has been the head of state of Nauru?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_632", "question": "Who is the father of Robert and also has been the head of state of Liechtenstein?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_633", "question": "Who is the father of Isabella of France, Queen of Navarre and also has been the head of state of Transnistria Governorate?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_634", "question": "Who is the father of Maecia Faustina and also has been the head of state of Kingdom of Ireland?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_635", "question": "Who is the father of Enzo Fernández and also has been the head of state of Kingdom of the Netherlands?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_636", "question": "Who is the father of Elagabalus and also has been the head of state of Kingdom of Greece?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_637", "question": "Who is the father of Julia the Elder and also has been the head of state of Kingdom of Great Britain?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_638", "question": "Who is the father of Julia Drusilla and also the child of Septimius Severus?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_639", "question": "Who is the father of Claudia Octavia and also the child of Caracalla?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_640", "question": "Who is the father of Pentawer and also the child of Ernst von Weizsäcker?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_641", "question": "Who is the father of Cicero Minor and also the child of Victoria, Princess Royal?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_642", "question": "Who is the father of Damian Marley and also the child of Joseph?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_643", "question": "Who is the father of Vasily Dzhugashvili and also the child of Juno?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_644", "question": "Who is the father of Michael Chaplin and also the child of Hjalmar Hammarskjöld?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_645", "question": "Who is the father of Philippe de Gaulle and also the child of Vespasian?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_646", "question": "Who is the father of Gilbert Mitterrand and also the child of Agrippina the Elder?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_647", "question": "Who is the father of Uday Hussein and also the child of Germanicus?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_648", "question": "Who is the father of Sean Lennon and also the child of Elagabalus?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_649", "question": "Who is the father of Germanicus and also the child of Joseph Léopold Sigisbert Hugo?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_650", "question": "Who is the father of Geta and also the child of Maecia Faustina?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_651", "question": "Who is the father of Britannicus and also the child of Benigno Aquino Jr.?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_652", "question": "Who is the father of Lucius Caesar and also the child of Joe Jackson?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_653", "question": "Who is the father of Drusus Julius Caesar and also the child of Rajmund Kaczyński?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_654", "question": "Who is the father of Leonard Darwin and also the child of Gordian I?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_655", "question": "Who is the father of George Howard Darwin and also the child of Leopold Mozart?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_656", "question": "Who is the father of Robert Todd Lincoln and also the child of Robert Darwin?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_657", "question": "Who is the father of Alexandre Colonna-Walewski and also the child of Hannah Chaplin?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_658", "question": "Who is the father of Jean-Louis Lully and also the author of Emancipation Proclamation?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_659", "question": "Who is the father of Francis Darwin and also the author of Bixby letter?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_660", "question": "Who is the father of Manilal Gandhi and also the author of Weaving the Web?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_661", "question": "Who is the father of Qusay Hussein and also the author of Chromium Embedded Framework?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_662", "question": "Who is the father of Julian Lennon and also the author of A Promised Land?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_663", "question": "Who is the father of Kojo Annan and also the author of Tim Berners-Lee: The year open data went worldwide?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_664", "question": "Who is the father of Evander of Pallene and also the author of Tim Berners-Lee: A Magna Carta for the web?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_665", "question": "Who is the father of María Isabel Allende and also the author of Tim Berners-Lee: The next web?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_666", "question": "Who is the father of Karl Mozart and also the author of Un Cheval dans la salle de bains?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_667", "question": "Who is the father of Nick Sagan and also the author of Wikipedia?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_668", "question": "Who is the father of Edward Baker Lincoln and also the author of Wiktionary?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_669", "question": "Who is the father of Josephine Chaplin and also the author of Contact?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_670", "question": "Who is the father of Pietro Alighieri and also the author of Billions and Billions: Thoughts on Life and Death at the Brink of the Millennium?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_671", "question": "Who is the father of Georgina Bloomberg and also the author of Wikibooks?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_672", "question": "Who is the father of Charlotte Gainsbourg and also the author of Racine and Shakespeare?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_673", "question": "Who is the father of Philippus II and also the author of Wikiquote?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_674", "question": "Who is the father of Vivian Kubrick and also the author of The Red and the Black?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_675", "question": "Who is the father of Agrippa Postumus and also the author of Wikispecies?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_676", "question": "Who is the father of Devdas Gandhi and also the author of Things Seen?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_677", "question": "Who is the father of Chagatai Khan and also the author of Mission Accomplished speech?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_678", "question": "Who is the father of Victoria Chaplin and also the employer of Chad Hurley?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_679", "question": "Who is the father of Jesse Dylan and also the employer of Justin Rosenstein?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_680", "question": "Who is the father of Peter, Count of Perche and Alençon and also the employer of Lars Bak?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_681", "question": "Who is the father of Ky-Mani Marley and also the employer of Marc Blank?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_682", "question": "Who is the father of Jean-Jacques Ampère and also the employer of Patricia Harris?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_683", "question": "Who is the father of Gaius Caesar and also the employer of George Forsythe?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_684", "question": "Who is the father of Siegfried Wagner and also the employer of Horst Teltschik?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_685", "question": "Who is the father of Lucius Aelius Caesar and also the employer of J. Michael Luttig?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_686", "question": "Who is the father of Johann Gottfried Bernhard Bach and also the employer of Laszlo Bock?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_687", "question": "Who is the father of Jean-Baptiste Lully fils and also the employer of Dan Fredinburg?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_688", "question": "Who is the father of Lolita Séchan and also the employer of Salar Kamangar?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_689", "question": "Who is the father of Jakob Dylan and also the employer of Jarkko Oikarinen?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_690", "question": "Who is the father of John Tristan, Count of Valois and also the employer of Brad Fitzpatrick?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_691", "question": "Who is the father of Anne Darwin and also the employer of Don Woods?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_692", "question": "Who is the father of Enriqueta Pinto Garmendia and also the employer of Susan Wojcicki?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_693", "question": "Who is the father of Horace Darwin and also the employer of Sebastian Thrun?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_694", "question": "Who is the father of Giulio Einaudi and also the employer of Naima Mora?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_695", "question": "Who is the father of James M. Bardeen and also the employer of Iman?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_696", "question": "Who is the father of Konstantin Kuzakov and also the employer of Marisa Miller?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_697", "question": "Who is the father of Faustina the Younger and also the employer of Mary Lou Jepsen?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_698", "question": "Who is the father of Lucilla and also the founder of United States Department of Homeland Security?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_699", "question": "Who is the father of Alahaibieji and also the founder of European Air Transport Command?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_700", "question": "Who is the father of Nicomachus and also the founder of Google Translate?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_701", "question": "Who is the father of Hamnet Shakespeare and also the founder of European Coal and Steel Community?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_702", "question": "Who is the father of Ricciotti Garibaldi and also the founder of House of Bonaparte?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_703", "question": "Who is the father of Vitellia Galeria and also the founder of Berliner Verkehrsbetriebe?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_704", "question": "Who is the father of Bongbong Marcos and also the founder of United Arab Republic?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_705", "question": "Who is the father of Louis Lully and also the founder of Catholic Church?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_706", "question": "Who is the father of Jessica Springsteen and also the founder of Digital Living Network Alliance?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_707", "question": "Who is the father of Jacopo Alighieri and also the founder of Zangger Committee?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_708", "question": "Who is the father of Lucius Calpurnius Piso Frugi Licinianus and also the founder of Wassenaar Arrangement?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_709", "question": "Who is the father of Jules Barthélemy-Saint-Hilaire and also the founder of International Internet Preservation Consortium?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_710", "question": "Who is the father of Charles Léon and also the founder of Dirección de Inteligencia Nacional?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_711", "question": "Who is the father of Charles Chaplin and also the founder of French Order of Academic Palms?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_712", "question": "Who is the father of Sydney Chaplin and also the founder of Casa de las Américas?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_713", "question": "Who is the father of Léopoldine Hugo and also the founder of IECEE/CEE?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_714", "question": "Who is the father of Jorge Manuel Theocupulus and also the founder of Siri?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_715", "question": "Who is the father of Christopher Chaplin and also the founder of The Planetary Society?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_716", "question": "Who is the father of Tümelün and also the founder of German Cross?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_717", "question": "Who is the father of Susanna Hall and also the founder of Sainte Chapelle?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_718", "question": "Who is the father of Anne de Gaulle and also the cast member in Sex and the City?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_719", "question": "Who is the father of Claude Chirac and also the cast member in The Devil Wears Prada?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_720", "question": "Who is the father of Henri Giscard d'Estaing and also the cast member in No Direction Home?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_721", "question": "Who is the father of Ricardo Lagos Weber and also the cast member in Jenna's American Sex Star?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_722", "question": "Who is the father of Jeremy Sagan and also the cast member in Dont Look Back?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_723", "question": "Who is the father of William Wallace Lincoln and also the cast member in Inside Deep Throat?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_724", "question": "Who is the father of Judith Quiney and also the cast member in The Iron Lady?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_725", "question": "Who is the father of Kölgen and also the cast member in Gossip Girl?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_726", "question": "Who is the father of Harilal Gandhi and also the cast member in The Day the Earth Stood Still?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_727", "question": "Who is the father of William A. Bardeen and also the cast member in A.I. Artificial Intelligence?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_728", "question": "Who is the father of Huochenbieji and also the cast member in Out of Africa?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_729", "question": "Who is the father of Rana Hussein and also the cast member in Iron Man 3?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_730", "question": "Who is the father of Amun-her-khepeshef and also the cast member in Marvin's Room?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_731", "question": "Who is the father of Adèle Hugo and also the cast member in Dancing at Lughnasa?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_732", "question": "Who is the father of Artem Sergeev and also the cast member in Rendition?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_733", "question": "Who is the father of Princess Paula of Brazil and also the cast member in Deep Throat?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_734", "question": "Who is the father of Margaret of France, Duchess of Brabant and also the cast member in Zombie Strippers?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_735", "question": "Who is the father of Stephen Marley and also the cast member in Capitalism: A Love Story?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_736", "question": "Who is the father of Katarzyna Tusk and also the cast member in The 11th Hour?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_737", "question": "Who is the father of Michał Tusk and also the cast member in Nixon?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_738", "question": "Who is the mother of Anna of Savoy and also has been the spouse of Eva Braun?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_739", "question": "Who is the mother of Surya and also has been the spouse of Laura Bush?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_740", "question": "Who is the mother of Liza Minnelli and also has been the spouse of Marie Louise I, Duchess of Parma?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_741", "question": "Who is the mother of James Hamilton, 2nd Duke of Abercorn and also has been the spouse of Joséphine de Beauharnais?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_742", "question": "Who is the mother of Lord George Hamilton and also has been the spouse of Faustina the Younger?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_743", "question": "Who is the mother of Leopold, Duke of Lorraine and also has been the spouse of Oona O'Neill?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_744", "question": "Who is the mother of Maggie Simpson and also has been the spouse of Xanthippe?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_745", "question": "Who is the mother of Ares and also has been the spouse of Hannelore Kohl?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_746", "question": "Who is the mother of Willem-Alexander of the Netherlands and also has been the spouse of Messalina?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_747", "question": "Who is the mother of Philippe of Belgium and also has been the spouse of Christiane Herzog?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_748", "question": "Who is the mother of Dionysus and also has been the spouse of Marlies Schild?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_749", "question": "Who is the mother of Deimos and also has been the spouse of Christina Rau?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_750", "question": "Who is the mother of Phobos and also has been the spouse of Charlene, Princess of Monaco?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_751", "question": "Who is the mother of Cleopatra Selene II and also has been the spouse of Rainier III, Prince of Mónaco?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_752", "question": "Who is the mother of Alfred Aetheling and also has been the spouse of Bellona?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_753", "question": "Who is the mother of Ptolemy VI and also has been the spouse of Martha Washington?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_754", "question": "Who is the mother of Hecate and also has been the spouse of Calpurnia?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_755", "question": "Who is the mother of Bilawal Bhutto Zardari and also has been the spouse of Cornelia?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_756", "question": "Who is the mother of Antigone and also has been the spouse of Maria Kaczyńska?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_757", "question": "Who is the mother of Aeneas and also has been the spouse of Linda McCartney?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_758", "question": "Who is the mother of Eileithyia and also the head of state of Belize?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_759", "question": "Who is the mother of Charles I of Naples and also the head of state of State of Palestine?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_760", "question": "Who is the mother of historical Jesus and also the head of state of Confederate States?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_761", "question": "Who is the mother of Emperor Zhongzong of Tang and also the head of state of Kingdom of Italy?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_762", "question": "Who is the mother of Emperor Ruizong of Tang and also the head of state of Kingdom of Westphalia?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_763", "question": "Who is the mother of Edward the Confessor and also the head of state of Electorate of Saxony?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_764", "question": "Who is the mother of Princess Stéphanie of Monaco and also the head of state of Manchukuo?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_765", "question": "Who is the mother of Henrietta Godolphin, 2nd Duchess of Marlborough and also the head of state of Inca Empire?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_766", "question": "Who is the mother of Elizabeth I of Russia and also the head of state of Kingdom of Portugal?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_767", "question": "Who is the mother of Ève Curie and also the head of state of Azad Kashmir?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_768", "question": "Who is the mother of Caroline, Princess of Hanover and also the head of state of North Korea?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_769", "question": "Who is the mother of Varuna and also the head of state of First French Empire?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_770", "question": "Who is the mother of Charles Chaplin and also the head of state of Cambodia?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_771", "question": "Who is the mother of Edward VII and also the head of state of Mordor?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_772", "question": "Who is the mother of Tina Weirather and also the head of state of French constitutional monarchy?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_773", "question": "Who is the mother of Persephone and also the head of state of Venezuela?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_774", "question": "Who is the mother of Anne, Princess Royal and also the head of state of Iran?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_775", "question": "Who is the mother of Victoria, Princess Royal and also the head of state of French Fifth Republic?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_776", "question": "Who is the mother of Meketaten and also the head of state of New Zealand?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_777", "question": "Who is the mother of Meritaten and also the head of state of Gran Colombia?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_778", "question": "Who is the mother of Agrippina the Elder and also the child of Bardock?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_779", "question": "Who is the mother of Lucius Caesar and also the child of Martha Frahm?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_780", "question": "Who is the mother of Agrippa Postumus and also the child of Grandpa Gohan?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_781", "question": "Who is the mother of Gaius Caesar and also the child of Klara Hitler?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_782", "question": "Who is the mother of Eros and also the child of Anna Maria Mozart?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_783", "question": "Who is the mother of Hermaphroditus and also the child of Louis VIII of France?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_784", "question": "Who is the mother of Priapus and also the child of Aurelia?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_785", "question": "Who is the mother of Prince Constantijn of the Netherlands and also the child of Antonia Minor?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_786", "question": "Who is the mother of Prince Friso of the Netherlands and also the child of Atia?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_787", "question": "Who is the mother of Ādityas and also the child of John Romita, Sr.?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_788", "question": "Who is the mother of Konstantinos Doukas and also the child of Jadwiga Kaczyńska?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_789", "question": "Who is the mother of Prince Laurent of Belgium and also the child of Henri de Gaulle?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_790", "question": "Who is the mother of Hygieia and also the child of Corazon Aquino?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_791", "question": "Who is the mother of Charites and also the child of Ramesses III?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_792", "question": "Who is the mother of Charles III of the United Kingdom and also the child of Stanley Ann Dunham?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_793", "question": "Who is the mother of Juan Antonio Bardem and also the child of Augustine Washington?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_794", "question": "Who is the mother of Alice of the United Kingdom and also the child of Eleanor of England?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_795", "question": "Who is the mother of Princess Beatrice of the United Kingdom and also the child of Tiberius Claudius Nero?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_796", "question": "Who is the mother of Charles Joseph of Lorraine and also the child of Jens Amundsen?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_797", "question": "Who is the mother of Monthu and also the child of Gaius Julius Caesar?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_798", "question": "Who is the mother of Anthony Hickox and also the employer of James Gosling?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_799", "question": "Who is the mother of Sydney Chaplin and also the employer of Larry Page?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_800", "question": "Who is the mother of Ptolemy of Mauretania and also the employer of Ken Thompson?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_801", "question": "Who is the mother of Jake Paltrow and also the employer of Kai-Fu Lee?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_802", "question": "Who is the mother of Antiochus XIII Asiaticus and also the employer of Petri Kokko?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_803", "question": "Who is the mother of Anna Petrovna of Russia and also the employer of Guy Kawasaki?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_804", "question": "Who is the mother of Prince Harry, Duke of Sussex and also the employer of Dennis Hwang?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_805", "question": "Who is the mother of James Hickox and also the employer of Steve Chen?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_806", "question": "Who is the mother of Lord Frederick Spencer Hamilton and also the employer of Lu Parker?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_807", "question": "Who is the mother of Spider-Girl and also the employer of Adriano Espaillat?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_808", "question": "Who is the mother of Harthacanute and also the employer of Cornelius Lanczos?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_809", "question": "Who is the mother of William, Prince of Wales and also the employer of Thomas R. Pickering?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_810", "question": "Who is the mother of Prince Andrew, Duke of York and also the employer of Peter Barron?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_811", "question": "Who is the mother of Infante Carlos of Spain and also the employer of Panagiotis Ipeirotis?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_812", "question": "Who is the mother of Vayu and also the employer of René Obermann?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_813", "question": "Who is the mother of Pilar Bardem and also the employer of Sergei Winogradsky?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_814", "question": "Who is the mother of Neferneferure and also the employer of Luis von Ahn?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_815", "question": "Who is the mother of Neferneferuaten Tasherit and also the employer of Elsa Hosk?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_816", "question": "Who is the mother of Ptolemy Philadelphus and also the employer of Nayef Al-Rodhan?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_817", "question": "Who is the mother of Alexander Helios and also the employer of Jean Pierson?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_818", "question": "Who is the mother of Alphonse, Count of Poitiers and also the founder of Nupedia?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_819", "question": "Who is the mother of Julia the Younger and also the founder of Haus der Kunst?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_820", "question": "Who is the mother of Isabelle of France and also the founder of Chromium?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_821", "question": "Who is the mother of Tyche and also the founder of English Wikipedia Arbitration Committee?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_822", "question": "Who is the mother of Berenice III and also the founder of Australia Group?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_823", "question": "Who is the mother of Rumer Willis and also the founder of École Spéciale Militaire de Saint-Cyr?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_824", "question": "Who is the mother of Gunhilda of Denmark and also the founder of Institut d'Égypte?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_825", "question": "Who is the mother of Jacob and also the founder of Citizendium?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_826", "question": "Who is the mother of Ptolemy of Cyprus and also the founder of Zikim?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_827", "question": "Who is the mother of Harmonia and also the founder of Abercrombie & Fitch?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_828", "question": "Who is the mother of Maria Riva and also the founder of Missile Technology Control Regime?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_829", "question": "Who is the mother of Robert I, Count of Artois and also the founder of Franco-German University?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_830", "question": "Who is the mother of Hebe and also the founder of German Foundation for Peace Research?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_831", "question": "Who is the mother of Sanjay Gandhi and also the founder of Israelite Central Consistory of France?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_832", "question": "Who is the mother of Leo II and also the founder of Conseil d'État?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_833", "question": "Who is the mother of Cleopatra Thea and also the founder of grande école?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_834", "question": "Who is the mother of Ankhesenamun and also the founder of ClubJenna?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_835", "question": "Who is the mother of Fatima and also the founder of Socialist Party of Chile?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_836", "question": "Who is the mother of Plutus and also the founder of École des arts industriels et des mines?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_837", "question": "Who is the mother of Esau and also the founder of University of France?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_838", "question": "Who is the mother of Chelsea Clinton and also the cast member in Man of Iron?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_839", "question": "Who is the mother of Princess Louise, Duchess of Argyll and also the cast member in Private Parts?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_840", "question": "Who is the mother of Prince Arthur, Duke of Connaught and Strathearn and also the cast member in The Butler?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_841", "question": "Who is the mother of Mamie Gummer and also the cast member in Edge of Tomorrow?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_842", "question": "Who is the mother of Alfred, Duke of Saxe-Coburg and Gotha and also the cast member in D.C. Cab?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_843", "question": "Who is the mother of Tryphaena and also the cast member in Ratboy?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_844", "question": "Who is the mother of Eryx and also the cast member in New Year's Eve?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_845", "question": "Who is the mother of Antiochus X Eusebes and also the cast member in Gates of Paris?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_846", "question": "Who is the mother of Hymen and also the cast member in Mamma Mia!?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_847", "question": "Who is the mother of Prince Edward, Duke of Edinburgh and also the cast member in Sophie's Choice?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_848", "question": "Who is the mother of Princess Margaret, Countess of Snowdon and also the cast member in Pat Garrett and Billy the Kid?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_849", "question": "Who is the mother of Princess Taiping and also the cast member in Hearts of Fire?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_850", "question": "Who is the mother of Li Hong and also the cast member in Catchfire?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_851", "question": "Who is the mother of Hélène Langevin-Joliot and also the cast member in George Harrison: Living in the Material World?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_852", "question": "Who is the mother of Louisa Montagu Douglas Scott, Duchess of Buccleuch and also the cast member in Marley?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_853", "question": "Who is the mother of Francis II of the Two Sicilies and also the cast member in Stay Away, Joe?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_854", "question": "Who is the mother of Lorna Luft and also the cast member in Easy Come, Easy Go?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_855", "question": "Who is the mother of Liber and also the cast member in Spinout?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_856", "question": "Who is the mother of Mitra and also the cast member in Clambake?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_857", "question": "Who is the mother of Ptolemy Eupator and also the cast member in Speedway?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_858", "question": "Who is married to Ekaterina Svanidze and is also the child of Johann Ambrosius Bach?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_859", "question": "Who is married to Patti Scialfa and is also the child of Barbara Bush?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_860", "question": "Who is married to Isetnofret and is also the child of Alberto Bachelet?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_861", "question": "Who is married to Meritamen and is also the child of Johann van Beethoven?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_862", "question": "Who is married to Galeria Fundana and is also the child of Livia?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_863", "question": "Who is married to Bintanath and is also the child of Saint Anne?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_864", "question": "Who is married to Mirka Federer and is also the child of John Shakespeare?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_865", "question": "Who is married to Vibia Sabina and is also the child of Besarion Jughashvili?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_866", "question": "Who is married to Ice-T and is also the child of Kushina Uzumaki?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_867", "question": "Who is married to Pompeia Plotina and is also the child of God the Father?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_868", "question": "Who is married to Milonia Caesonia and is also the child of Shiva?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_869", "question": "Who is married to Ray Brown and is also the child of Agrippina the Younger?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_870", "question": "Who is married to Bernadette Chirac and is also the child of Nero Claudius Drusus?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_871", "question": "Who is married to Sajida Talfah and is also the child of Seti I?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_872", "question": "Who is married to Cynthia Lennon and is also the child of Sextilia?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_873", "question": "Who is married to Margaret of Provence and is also the child of Ilya Ulyanov?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_874", "question": "Who is married to Mary Todd Lincoln and is also the child of Arseny Tarkovsky?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_875", "question": "Who is married to Sara Dylan and is also the child of Lucius Salvius Otho?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_876", "question": "Who is married to Anne-Aymone Giscard d'Estaing and is also the child of Maria Elisabeth Lämmerhirt?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_877", "question": "Who is married to Eun Ji-won and is also the child of The Smoking Man?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_878", "question": "Who is the spouse of Daryl Hannah and also the employer of William H. Johnson?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_879", "question": "Who is the spouse of Christina Hendricks and also the employer of Matías Duarte?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_880", "question": "Who is the spouse of Imelda Marcos and also the employer of Peter Norvig?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_881", "question": "Who is the spouse of Thetis and also the employer of Vint Cerf?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_882", "question": "Who is the spouse of Olivia Harrison and also the employer of Robert Boyle?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_883", "question": "Who is the spouse of Liutperga and also the employer of Andrew Rubin?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_884", "question": "Who is the spouse of Swanachild and also the employer of Ben Goodger?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_885", "question": "Who is the spouse of Fulvia Plautilla and also the employer of Mohit Aron?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_886", "question": "Who is the spouse of Domitia Longina and also the employer of Ian J. Goodfellow?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_887", "question": "Who is the spouse of María Kodama and also the employer of Urs Hölzle?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_888", "question": "Who is the spouse of Pythias and also the employer of Wesley Chan?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_889", "question": "Who is the spouse of Franca Rame and also the employer of Vic Gundotra?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_890", "question": "Who is the spouse of Yelena Bonner and also the employer of Yossi Matias?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_891", "question": "Who is the spouse of Rita Marley and also the employer of Wayne Rosing?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_892", "question": "Who is the spouse of Annia Faustina and also the employer of Craig Chambers?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_893", "question": "Who is the spouse of Marcia Otacilia Severa and also the employer of Samy Bengio?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_894", "question": "Who is the spouse of Aquilia Severa and also the employer of Peter Mattis?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_895", "question": "Who is the spouse of Sallustia Orbiana and also the employer of Petr Mitrichev?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_896", "question": "Who is the spouse of Herennia Etruscilla and also the employer of Rachel Whetstone?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_897", "question": "Who is the spouse of Rita Wilson and also the employer of Preston McAfee?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_898", "question": "Who is married to Marina Vlady and is also the cast member in Der Sieg des Glaubens?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_899", "question": "Who is married to Julie Gayet and is also the cast member in Enigma?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_900", "question": "Who is married to Chuck Traynor and is also the cast member in Inside Nazi Germany?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_901", "question": "Who is married to Anita Garibaldi and is also the cast member in Paradise, Hawaiian Style?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_902", "question": "Who is married to Sitre and is also the cast member in Fun in Acapulco?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_903", "question": "Who is married to Marcellus and is also the cast member in Flaming Star?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_904", "question": "Who is married to Danielle Mitterrand and is also the cast member in A Special Day?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_905", "question": "Who is married to Hinata Hyūga and is also the cast member in Lions for Lambs?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_906", "question": "Who is married to Feroze Gandhi and is also the cast member in Julie & Julia?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_907", "question": "Who is married to Kamala Nehru and is also the cast member in Two Comrades Were Serving?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_908", "question": "Who is married to Harriet Smithson and is also the cast member in Roseanne?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_909", "question": "Who is married to Anne Hathaway and is also the cast member in Dharma & Greg?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_910", "question": "Who is married to Barbara Bach and is also the cast member in Religulous?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_911", "question": "Who is married to Pattie Boyd and is also the cast member in Stuck on You?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_912", "question": "Who is married to Hildegard of Vinzgouw and is also the cast member in This Must Be the Place?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_913", "question": "Who is married to Livia Orestilla and is also the cast member in The Dictator?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_914", "question": "Who is married to Statilia Messalina and is also the cast member in Spin City?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_915", "question": "Who is married to Priscilla Presley and is also the cast member in The Island of Dr. Moreau?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_916", "question": "Who is married to Lynn Margulis and is also the cast member in John Q?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_917", "question": "Who is married to Lisa Marie Presley and is also the cast member in The Virgin of Nuremberg?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_918", "question": "Who is married to Cécilia Attias and also the founder of AFRISTAT?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_919", "question": "Who is married to Börte and also the founder of Latin American Free Trade Association?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_920", "question": "Who is married to Julianne Phillips and also the founder of Palais des Beaux-Arts de Lille?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_921", "question": "Who is married to Don Gummer and also the founder of Rite of Memphis-Misraim?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_922", "question": "Who is married to Edie Brickell and also the founder of Nantes Museum of Arts?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_923", "question": "Who is married to Tyti and also the founder of Paris Chamber of Commerce?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_924", "question": "Who is married to Livia and also the founder of Order of Bernardo O'Higgins?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_925", "question": "Who is married to Marcia Furnilla and also the founder of Church of St. Sophia?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_926", "question": "Who is married to Flavia Titiana and also the founder of First Geneva Convention?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_927", "question": "Who is married to Fanny Stevenson and also the founder of International Cospas-Sarsat Programme?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_928", "question": "Who is married to Pythagoras and also the founder of Chingissid?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_929", "question": "Who is married to Manlia Scantilla and also the founder of ASECNA?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_930", "question": "Who is married to Alice Hoschedé and also the founder of Maisons d'éducation de la Légion d'honneur?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_931", "question": "Who is married to Armande Béjart and also the founder of Institut industriel du Nord?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_932", "question": "Who is married to Danuta Wałęsa and also the founder of United States Department of Agriculture?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_933", "question": "Who is married to Fastrada and also the founder of European Gendarmerie Force?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_934", "question": "Who is married to Laodice III and also the founder of Rangoli?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_935", "question": "Who is married to Casimir Dudevant and also the founder of NMBS/SNCB?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_936", "question": "Who is married to Consuelo de Saint Exupéry and also the founder of Cricket World Cup?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_937", "question": "Who is married to Emma Heming Willis and also the founder of French Council of the Muslim Faith?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_938", "question": "Which country does Alice Panikian have citizenship in and is also the founder of Committee for Skeptical Inquiry from?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_939", "question": "Which country does Evelyne Brochu have citizenship in and is also the founder of Id Kah Mosque from?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_940", "question": "Which country does Albert Bandura have citizenship in and is also the founder of German Federal Environmental Foundation from?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_941", "question": "Which country does Stephen Harper have citizenship in and is also the founder of Rostelecom from?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_942", "question": "Which country does Sandra Oh have citizenship in and is also the founder of Sociedad Estatal de Participaciones Industriales from?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_943", "question": "Which country does Michelle MacLaren have citizenship in and is also the founder of Coalition for Epidemic Preparedness Innovations from?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_944", "question": "Which country does David Johnston have citizenship in and is also the founder of Google Buzz from?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_945", "question": "Which country does Sid Meier have citizenship in and is also the founder of Turkish State Railways from?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_946", "question": "Which country does Walter Mandler have citizenship in and is also the founder of Astrium from?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_947", "question": "Which country does Hans Selye have citizenship in and is also the founder of Alliance for Open Media from?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_948", "question": "Which country does William Kahan have citizenship in and is also the founder of GraphQL from?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_949", "question": "Which country does Jean Chrétien have citizenship in and is also the founder of Papahānaumokuākea Marine National Monument from?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_950", "question": "Which country does Tara Strong have citizenship in and is also the founder of Wikimedia Incubator from?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_951", "question": "Which country does Leonard Cohen have citizenship in and is also the founder of Bomis from?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_952", "question": "Which country does Maud Menten have citizenship in and is also the founder of Google Code Jam from?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_953", "question": "Which country does Sandford Fleming have citizenship in and is also the founder of Royal Museum of Fine Arts Antwerp from?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_954", "question": "Which country does Jacqueline Wong have citizenship in and is also the founder of São João Baptista d’Ajudá from?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_955", "question": "Which country does Charles Brenton Huggins have citizenship in and is also the founder of Union Army from?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_956", "question": "Which country does Neil Young have citizenship in and is also the founder of Flutter from?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_957", "question": "Which country does Céline Dion have citizenship in and is also the founder of Obama Foundation from?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_958", "question": "Who has been the head of state Duchy of Cleves and also the child of Antonio Ascari?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_959", "question": "Who has been the head of state Juho Kusti Paasikivi's third cabinet and also the child of Motilal Nehru?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_960", "question": "Who has been the head of state Weimar Republic and also the child of Gaius Octavius?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_961", "question": "Who has been the head of state Jordan and also the child of Tyti?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_962", "question": "Who has been the head of state Cabinet of Helle Thorning-Schmidt and also the child of Lucius Aelius Caesar?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_963", "question": "Who has been the head of state Kingdom of Scotland and also the child of Marcus Ulpius Traianus?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_964", "question": "Who has been the head of state Independent State of Croatia and also the child of Livia Ocellina?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_965", "question": "Who has been the head of state Margraviate of Baden-Durlach and also the child of Gustav Schwarzenegger?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_966", "question": "Who has been the head of state Vichy France and also the child of Publius Cornelius Scipio?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_967", "question": "Who has been the head of state Second French Empire and also the child of Charles Russell Bardeen?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_968", "question": "Who has been the head of state Valinor and also the child of Publius Aelius Hadrianus Afer?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_969", "question": "Who has been the head of state Kingdom of Hungary and also the child of José Cojuangco?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_970", "question": "Who has been the head of state Oprichnina and also the child of Thomas Stevenson?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_971", "question": "Who has been the head of state Ukrainian Soviet Socialist Republic and also the child of Setnakhte?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_972", "question": "Who has been the head of state Tokugawa shogunate and also the child of Julia Soaemias?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_973", "question": "Who has been the head of state Central African Empire and also the child of Julia Avita Mamaea?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_974", "question": "Who has been the head of state Estonian Soviet Socialist Republic and also the child of Julia Domna?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_975", "question": "Who has been the head of state Solomon Islands and also the child of Charles Chaplin Sr.?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_976", "question": "Who has been the head of state Principality of Bulgaria and also the child of Jorge Guillermo Borges Haslam?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_977", "question": "Who has been the head of state Australia and also the child of Cha Hwa-yeon?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_978", "question": "Who has been the head of state Tuvalu and also the author of Executive Order 13470?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_979", "question": "Who has been the head of state Syria and also the author of Decision Points?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_980", "question": "Who has been the head of state East Timor and also the author of Executive Order 13355?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_981", "question": "Who has been the head of state Mutawakkilite Kingdom of Yemen and also the author of Executive Order 13224?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_982", "question": "Who has been the head of state Democratic Kampuchea and also the author of Le Rhin?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_983", "question": "Who has been the head of state German Reich and also the author of Nupedia?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_984", "question": "Who has been the head of state Nicaragua and also the author of Pale Blue Dot?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_985", "question": "Who has been the head of state Bhutan and also the author of Ordeal?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_986", "question": "Who has been the head of state Dominion of India and also the author of Jimmy Wales: The birth of Wikipedia?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_987", "question": "Who has been the head of state first Kenny ministry and also the author of David Cameron: The next age of government?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_988", "question": "Who has been the head of state Papua New Guinea and also the author of Ken Jennings: Watson, Jeopardy and me, the obsolete know-it-all?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_989", "question": "Who has been the head of state German Empire of 1848/1849 and also the author of Fandom?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_990", "question": "Who has been the head of state Cals cabinet and also the author of The Charterhouse of Parma?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_991", "question": "Who has been the head of state Saint Kitts and Nevis and also the author of Armance?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_992", "question": "Who has been the head of state Novgorod Rus' and also the author of On Love?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_993", "question": "Who has been the head of state Hesham Qandil Ministry and also the author of Les Contemplations?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_994", "question": "Who has been the head of state Cameron–Clegg coalition and also the author of Demain dès l'aube?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_995", "question": "Who has been the head of state Brown ministry and also the author of Claude Gueux?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_996", "question": "Who has been the head of state Spain under Joseph Bonaparte and also the author of Le roi s'amuse?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_997", "question": "Who has been the head of state Military Government of Chile and also the author of Les Rougon-Macquart?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_998", "question": "Who has been the head of state Second Salmond ministry and also the screenwriter of 1984?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_999", "question": "Who has been the head of state First Sirimavo Bandaranaike cabinet and also the screenwriter of Inglourious Basterds?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1000", "question": "Who has been the head of state Federation of Nigeria and also the screenwriter of Otello?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1001", "question": "Who has been the head of state First Thatcher ministry and also the screenwriter of Ivan's Childhood?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1002", "question": "Who has been the head of state Dominion of Ghana and also the screenwriter of Hancock?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1003", "question": "Who has been the head of state Heath ministry and also the screenwriter of Kill Bill: The Whole Bloody Affair?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1004", "question": "Who has been the head of state People's Democratic Republic of Ethiopia and also the screenwriter of Pulp Fiction?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1005", "question": "Who has been the head of state Commonwealth realm of the Gambia and also the screenwriter of King Kong?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1006", "question": "Who has been the head of state Provisional Government of the Republic of China and also the screenwriter of The Lord of the Rings: The Return of the King?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1007", "question": "Who has been the head of state Government of the Republic of China in Guangzhou and also the screenwriter of Ernani?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1008", "question": "Who has been the head of state State of Malta and also the screenwriter of Andrei Rublev?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1009", "question": "Who has been the head of state Commonwealth realm of Malawi and also the screenwriter of Religulous?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1010", "question": "Who has been the head of state Dual monarchy of England and France and also the screenwriter of Moonwalker?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1011", "question": "Who has been the head of state Saint Vincent and the Grenadines and also the screenwriter of Michael Jackson's Ghosts?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1012", "question": "Who has been the head of state Dominion of Fiji and also the screenwriter of Bonjour tristesse?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1013", "question": "Who has been the head of state Muhammad in Medina and also the screenwriter of Barry Lyndon?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1014", "question": "Who has been the head of state Media and also the screenwriter of The Gold Rush?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1015", "question": "Who has been the head of state 2nd Lemass ministry and also the screenwriter of Monsieur Verdoux?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1016", "question": "Who has been the head of state Lal Bahadur Shastri Ministry and also the screenwriter of Chaplin?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1017", "question": "Who has been the head of state Russian State and also the screenwriter of Roméo et Juliete?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1018", "question": "Who has been the head of state of First Cabinet of Independent India and also the employer of Russ Cox?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1019", "question": "Who has been the head of state of Saint Lucia and also the employer of Chien Lee-feng?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1020", "question": "Who has been the head of state of Reunited Kingdom and also the employer of John Celivergos Zachos?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1021", "question": "Who has been the head of state of Second Biesheuvel cabinet and also the employer of Étienne Dormoy?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1022", "question": "Who has been the head of state of First Philippine Republic and also the employer of Dennis Muilenburg?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1023", "question": "Who has been the head of state of Government of the 3rd Scottish Parliament and also the employer of Adeline Smith?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1024", "question": "Who has been the head of state of Government of the 2nd Scottish Parliament and also the employer of Edward M. McCreight?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1025", "question": "Who has been the head of state of Blair governments and also the employer of Chris Lattner?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1026", "question": "Who has been the head of state of Kingdom of Bosnia and also the employer of Bram Moolenaar?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1027", "question": "Who has been the head of state of Japan and also the employer of Geoffrey Hinton?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1028", "question": "Who has been the head of state of Brunei and also the employer of Christopher Poole?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1029", "question": "Who has been the head of state of Tajikistan and also the employer of George Reyes?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1030", "question": "Who has been the head of state of Central African Republic and also the employer of Dennis Woodside?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1031", "question": "Who has been the head of state of Brundtland's Second Cabinet and also the employer of Mostafa Madbouly?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1032", "question": "Who has been the head of state of Gau Baden-Elsaß and also the employer of Orkut Büyükkökten?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1033", "question": "Who has been the head of state of Brundtland's First Cabinet and also the employer of Mark Davis?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1034", "question": "Who has been the head of state of First Van Agt cabinet and also the employer of Larry McVoy?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1035", "question": "Who has been the head of state of Principality of Smolensk and also the employer of Sundar Pichai?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1036", "question": "Who has been the head of state of De Jong cabinet and also the employer of Andrew Y. Ng?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1037", "question": "Who has been the head of state of Zijlstra cabinet and also the employer of Anna Patterson?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1038", "question": "Who has been the head of state of First Biesheuvel cabinet and also the founder of Nuclear Suppliers Group?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1039", "question": "Who has been the head of state of Sultanate of Nejd and also the founder of Matter?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1040", "question": "Who has been the head of state of Gerhardsen's Third Cabinet and also the founder of Royal Society of Edinburgh?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1041", "question": "Who has been the head of state of Willoch's Second Cabinet and also the founder of Alcora Exercise?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1042", "question": "Who has been the head of state of South Russia and also the founder of Pacific Alliance?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1043", "question": "Who has been the head of state of Kingdom of Italy and also the founder of Open Data Institute?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1044", "question": "Who has been the head of state of Grenada and also the founder of Global Network Initiative?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1045", "question": "Who has been the head of state of Gau Westmark and also the founder of World Wide Web Virtual Library?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1046", "question": "Who has been the head of state of Willoch's Cabinet and also the founder of World Wide Web Foundation?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1047", "question": "Who has been the head of state of Bratteli's First Cabinet and also the founder of Calico?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1048", "question": "Who has been the head of state of Brundtland's Third Cabinet and also the founder of Walt Disney Records?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1049", "question": "Who has been the head of state of Eritrea and also the founder of General Electric?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1050", "question": "Who has been the head of state of Zaire and also the founder of Higher Ground Productions?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1051", "question": "Who has been the head of state of First Indira Gandhi Ministry and also the founder of Global Partnership on Artificial Intelligence?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1052", "question": "Who has been the head of state of Government of Manuel Valls II and also the founder of Museo di Storia Naturale di Venezia?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1053", "question": "Who has been the head of state of Rashidun Caliphate and also the founder of Overture Maps Foundation?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1054", "question": "Who has been the head of state of South Sudan and also the founder of San Marino Post?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1055", "question": "Who has been the head of state of Equatorial Guinea and also the founder of Open Source Development Labs?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1056", "question": "Who has been the head of state of Tonga and also the founder of Sinclair Research?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1057", "question": "Who has been the head of state of Djibouti and also the founder of The Republicans?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1058", "question": "Who has been the head of state Antigua and Barbuda and also the cast member in G.I. Blues?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1059", "question": "Who has been the head of state Duvalier dynasty and also the cast member in Double Trouble?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1060", "question": "Who has been the head of state Jersey and also the cast member in The World Moves On?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1061", "question": "Who has been the head of state Jamaica and also the cast member in Pauly Shore Is Dead?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1062", "question": "Who has been the head of state Serbia and also the cast member in Film Socialisme?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1063", "question": "Who has been the head of state Manitoba and also the cast member in Le grand soir?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1064", "question": "Who has been the head of state Georgia and also the cast member in The Meeting Place Cannot Be Changed?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1065", "question": "Who has been the head of state Cabinet of the Confederate States and also the cast member in Prelude to War?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1066", "question": "Who has been the head of state Gibraltar and also the cast member in La Révolution française?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1067", "question": "Who has been the head of state Islamic Republic of Afghanistan and also the cast member in Love Me Tender?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1068", "question": "Who has been the head of state Western Chu and also the cast member in Viva Las Vegas?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1069", "question": "Who has been the head of state Soviet Union and also the cast member in Sink the Bismarck!?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1070", "question": "Who has been the head of state The Bahamas and also the cast member in The Garden of the Finzi-Continis?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1071", "question": "Who has been the head of state Taiwan and also the cast member in Live a Little, Love a Little?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1072", "question": "Who has been the head of state Nova Scotia and also the cast member in Cross of Iron?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1073", "question": "Who has been the head of state Republic of the Congo and also the cast member in Enron: The Smartest Guys in the Room?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1074", "question": "Who has been the head of state Gabon and also the cast member in Who Killed the Electric Car??", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1075", "question": "Who has been the head of state Duchy of Milan and also the cast member in Heartburn?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1076", "question": "Who has been the head of state Korean Empire and also the cast member in Doubt?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1077", "question": "Who has been the head of state Cape Verde and also the cast member in The Victors?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1078", "question": "Where is the capital of England and also the place of burial of Sakuramachi?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1079", "question": "Where is the capital of Norway and also the place of burial of Florentina?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1080", "question": "Where is the capital of Poland and also the place of burial of Fulgentius of Cartagena?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1081", "question": "Where is the capital of United States of America and also the place of burial of Edvard Isto?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1082", "question": "Where is the capital of Belgium and also the place of burial of Edward Frankland?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1083", "question": "Where is the capital of Lithuania and also the place of burial of Matthew Paris?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1084", "question": "Where is the capital of Switzerland and also the place of burial of Rob Roy MacGregor?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1085", "question": "Where is the capital of Uzbekistan and also the place of burial of Devlet II Giray?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1086", "question": "Where is the capital of Bulgaria and also the place of burial of Mikołaj Radziwiłł Czarny?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1087", "question": "Where is the capital of North Macedonia and also the place of burial of Patrick Juvet?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1088", "question": "Where is the capital of Indre-et-Loire and also the place of burial of Halim Giray?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1089", "question": "Where is the capital of Slovenia and also the place of burial of Qaplan II Giray?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1090", "question": "Where is the capital of Cologne Government Region and also the place of burial of Alexios II Komnenos?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1091", "question": "Where is the capital of Finistère and also the place of burial of Carlo II, Duke of Savoy?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1092", "question": "Where is the capital of Portugal and also the place of burial of Zeki Pasha?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1093", "question": "Where is the capital of Roman Empire and also the place of burial of Jaap Veldhuyzen van Zanten?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1094", "question": "Where is the capital of Emirate of Dubai and also the place of burial of Bruce Chatwin?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1095", "question": "Where is the capital of São Paulo and also the place of burial of Tito Vilanova?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1096", "question": "Where is the capital of Italy and also the place of burial of Thomas Koschat?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1097", "question": "Where is the capital of Greenland and also the place of burial of Maqsud Giray?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1098", "question": "Who is the child of Leonor Rita Acevedo Suárez and also the member of the sports team Canada?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1099", "question": "Who is the child of Parvati and also the member of the sports team Spain?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1100", "question": "Who is the child of Yeico Cáceres and also the member of the sports team Yorkshire?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1101", "question": "Who is the child of Titus Aurelius Fulvus and also the member of the sports team France?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1102", "question": "Who is the child of Charles August Lindbergh and also the member of the sports team Slovenia?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1103", "question": "Who is the child of Alfonso VIII of Castile and also the member of the sports team Toronto?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1104", "question": "Who is the child of Gnaeus Domitius Ahenobarbus and also the member of the sports team Vilnius?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1105", "question": "Who is the child of Marcus Annius Verus and also the member of the sports team Monaco?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1106", "question": "Who is the child of Calvisia Domitia Lucilla and also the member of the sports team Barbados?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1107", "question": "Who is the child of Tiy-Merenese and also the member of the sports team Tashkent?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1108", "question": "Who is the child of Nicolas Chopin and also the member of the sports team Sofia?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1109", "question": "Who is the child of Maria Ulyanova and also the member of the sports team Volga?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1110", "question": "Who is the child of Serafina Moritz and also the member of the sports team Inter Milan?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1111", "question": "Who is the child of Salvador Sanfuentes and also the member of the sports team Olympique Lyonnais?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1112", "question": "Who is the child of Joachim and also the member of the sports team Tbilisi?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1113", "question": "Who is the child of Mary Ball Washington and also the member of the sports team Chhattisgarh?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1114", "question": "Who is the child of Mariano Marcos and also the member of the sports team São Tomé and Príncipe?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1115", "question": "Who is the child of George Arnold Escher and also the member of the sports team Himachal Pradesh?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1116", "question": "Who is the child of Marcia and also the member of the sports team HC Lada Togliatti?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1117", "question": "Who is the child of Yu Yifu and is also the screenwriter of Cosmos: A Personal Voyage?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1118", "question": "Who is the child of Mohammed bin Awad bin Laden and is also the screenwriter of The Hitchhiker's Guide to the Galaxy?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1119", "question": "Who is the child of Étienne Pascal and is also the screenwriter of Stardust?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1120", "question": "Who is the child of Mummia Achaica and is also the screenwriter of X-Men: First Class?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1121", "question": "Who is the child of Tuya and is also the screenwriter of Eyes Wide Shut?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1122", "question": "Who is the child of Faustina the Younger and is also the screenwriter of A.I. Artificial Intelligence?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1123", "question": "Who is the child of Sextus Varius Marcellus and is also the screenwriter of Dune?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1124", "question": "Who is the child of Alighiero di Bellincione and is also the screenwriter of Dr. Strangelove?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1125", "question": "Who is the child of Kamala Nehru and is also the screenwriter of Kill Bill Volume 1?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1126", "question": "Who is the child of Julia Lennon and is also the screenwriter of The Lord of the Rings: The Two Towers?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1127", "question": "Who is the child of Glenn McQueen and is also the screenwriter of Reservoir Dogs?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1128", "question": "Who is the child of Nancy Hanks Lincoln and is also the screenwriter of Heavenly Creatures?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1129", "question": "Who is the child of Thomas Lincoln and is also the screenwriter of Jackie Brown?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1130", "question": "Who is the child of Conway Berners-Lee and is also the screenwriter of The Sacrifice?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1131", "question": "Who is the child of Popi Tsapanidou and is also the screenwriter of Contact?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1132", "question": "Who is the child of Barack Obama Sr. and is also the screenwriter of Burlesque on Carmen?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1133", "question": "Who is the child of Isaac Newton Sr. and is also the screenwriter of A Film Johnnie?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1134", "question": "Who is the child of Christopher Douglas Adams and is also the screenwriter of City Lights?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1135", "question": "Who is the child of Donald Tusk and is also the screenwriter of The Rounders?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1136", "question": "Who is the child of John Adams and is also the screenwriter of Easy Street?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1137", "question": "Who is the child of José Batlle y Ordóñez and is also the architect of Stade de Gerland?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1138", "question": "Who is the child of Alfred Lennon and is also the architect of Headquarters of the United Nations?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1139", "question": "Who is the child of Gaius Sulpicius Galba and is also the architect of Solomon R. Guggenheim Museum?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1140", "question": "Who is the child of Pierre-Joseph Ravel and is also the architect of Beth Sholom Congregation?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1141", "question": "Who is the child of Olivier Séchan and is also the architect of Chandigarh?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1142", "question": "Who is the child of Louis Gassion and is also the architect of Broadacre City?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1143", "question": "Who is the child of Line Marsa and is also the architect of Ennis House?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1144", "question": "Who is the child of Aurelia Schwarzenegger and is also the architect of Fallingwater?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1145", "question": "Who is the child of Janet Adams and is also the architect of The Illinois?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1146", "question": "Who is the child of Ptolemy VIII Physcon and is also the architect of Taliesin?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1147", "question": "Who is the child of Akhenaten and is also the architect of Capitoline Museums?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1148", "question": "Who is the child of Abigail Adams and is also the architect of Selimiye Mosque?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1149", "question": "Who is the child of Hermann Heller and is also the architect of Immeuble Clarté?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1150", "question": "Who is the child of Grace Kelly and is also the architect of Notre Dame du Haut?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1151", "question": "Who is the child of Chris de Burgh and is also the architect of Weissenhof Estate?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1152", "question": "Who is the child of Pushyamitra Shunga and is also the architect of Fondation suisse?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1153", "question": "Who is the child of Seleucus II Callinicus and is also the architect of St. Peter's Basilica?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1154", "question": "Who is the child of Musa al-Kadhim and is also the architect of Villa Savoye?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1155", "question": "Who is the child of Agnimitra and is also the architect of Mount Vernon?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1156", "question": "Who is the child of Indira Gandhi and is also the architect of Unité d'Habitation of Berlin?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1157", "question": "Who is the child of Ali al-Ridha and also the employer of Halldor Skard?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1158", "question": "Who is the child of Ramesses IV and also the employer of Amit Singhal?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1159", "question": "Who is the child of William Cecil, 5th Marquess of Exeter and also the employer of Spencer Kimball?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1160", "question": "Who is the child of Shigenobu Murofushi and also the employer of Rich Miner?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1161", "question": "Who is the child of John Russell, 6th Duke of Bedford and also the employer of Kent Walker?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1162", "question": "Who is the child of Zeus and also the employer of Anurag Acharya?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1163", "question": "Who is the child of Charlemagne and also the employer of Alexander Krizhevsky?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1164", "question": "Who is the child of Maximilian II of Bavaria and also the employer of Phil Harrison?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1165", "question": "Who is the child of Sophia of Hanover and also the employer of Junio C Hamano?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1166", "question": "Who is the child of Princess Ludovika of Bavaria and also the employer of Eric Brewer?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1167", "question": "Who is the child of Theon of Alexandria and also the employer of Nikesh Arora?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1168", "question": "Who is the child of Nabopolassar and also the employer of P.G. Sittenfeld?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1169", "question": "Who is the child of Hera and also the employer of Lars Rasmussen?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1170", "question": "Who is the child of Joseph P. Kennedy Sr. and also the employer of Quoc Viet Le?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1171", "question": "Who is the child of Rose Kennedy and also the employer of Bill Atkinson?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1172", "question": "Who is the child of Stefan Nemanja and also the employer of Eric Schmidt?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1173", "question": "Who is the child of Juana Enríquez and also the employer of Stanisław Wojciechowski?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1174", "question": "Who is the child of Robert Gascoyne-Cecil, 3rd Marquess of Salisbury and also the employer of John Barnett?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1175", "question": "Who is the child of Ferdinand Hodler and also the employer of Noah Falstein?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1176", "question": "Who is the child of Benjamin Harrison V and also the employer of Matt Pharr?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1177", "question": "Who is the child of Hugh Everett III and also the founder of React?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1178", "question": "Who is the child of The Younger Lady and also the founder of Gros Islet?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1179", "question": "Who is the child of Thomas Thynne, 1st Marquess of Bath and also the founder of Tuvalu Trust Fund?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1180", "question": "Who is the child of Poseidon and also the founder of Wikimedia Foundation Board of Trustees?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1181", "question": "Who is the child of Frederick V of the Palatinate and also the founder of National Citizen Service?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1182", "question": "Who is the child of Maximilian I Joseph of Bavaria and also the founder of Carter Center?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1183", "question": "Who is the child of Uranus and also the founder of Académie Française?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1184", "question": "Who is the child of Gianluigi Bonelli and also the founder of Republican Party?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1185", "question": "Who is the child of John Tyler and also the founder of United States Park Police?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1186", "question": "Who is the child of Antiochus III the Great and also the founder of Inter-Agency Space Debris Coordination Committee?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1187", "question": "Who is the child of Matilda of Ringelheim and also the founder of LEO LT?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1188", "question": "Who is the child of Frederick IV, Duke of Schleswig-Holstein-Gottorp and also the founder of Sveriges Radio?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1189", "question": "Who is the child of Princess Louise Auguste of Denmark and also the founder of DreamWorks?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1190", "question": "Who is the child of Charles Louis, Hereditary Prince of Baden and also the founder of Walt Disney World Resort?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1191", "question": "Who is the child of Landgravine Augusta Wilhelmina of Hesse-Darmstadt and also the founder of Initiative for Open Citations?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1192", "question": "Who is the child of Hildegard of Vinzgouw and also the founder of Chaldean Catholic Church?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1193", "question": "Who is the child of Ramesses IX and also the founder of freestyle wrestling?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1194", "question": "Who is the child of Otto Heinrich Frank and also the founder of Ralph Lauren (brand)?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1195", "question": "Who is the child of Pepin of Herstal and also the founder of Russian Orthodox Church?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1196", "question": "Who is the child of Gaia and also the founder of Culper Ring?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1197", "question": "Who is the child of Helga Nowitzki and also the cast member in Prime?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1198", "question": "Who is the child of Marie of Prussia and also the cast member in Death Becomes Her?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1199", "question": "Who is the child of Salome and also the cast member in Triumph Over Violence?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1200", "question": "Who is the child of Maximilian II Emanuel, Elector of Bavaria and also the cast member in WWII in HD?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1201", "question": "Who is the child of Friedrich Franz III, Grand Duke of Mecklenburg-Schwerin and also the cast member in Canciones para después de una guerra?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1202", "question": "Who is the child of Ptolemy V Epiphanes and also the cast member in After Porn Ends?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1203", "question": "Who is the child of Wilhelm, Duke of Urach and also the cast member in Deep Throat Part II?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1204", "question": "Who is the child of Magdalene Sibylle of Holstein-Gottorp and also the cast member in King Creole?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1205", "question": "Who is the child of Leopold III of Belgium and also the cast member in Mission to Moscow?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1206", "question": "Who is the child of Edith Frank-Holländer and also the cast member in Defiance?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1207", "question": "Who is the child of Pepin the Short and also the cast member in Mother Night?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1208", "question": "Who is the child of Cleopatra I Syra and also the cast member in The Broken Circle Breakdown?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1209", "question": "Who is the child of Hafez al-Assad and also the cast member in Oldboy?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1210", "question": "Who is the child of Erwin Rommel and also the cast member in I'm Still Here?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1211", "question": "Who is the child of Henry I the Fowler and also the cast member in Seeing Red?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1212", "question": "Who is the child of Étienne Gnassingbé Eyadéma and also the cast member in Neil Young Trunk Show?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1213", "question": "Who is the child of Saturn and also the cast member in Reagan?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1214", "question": "Who is the child of Bertrada of Laon and also the cast member in Neil Young: Heart of Gold?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1215", "question": "Who is the child of Laodice III and also the cast member in Blue Crush?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1216", "question": "Who is the child of Johann I of Saxony and also the cast member in The Big Empty?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1217", "question": "Who is the author of Thérèse Raquin and also the director of City of Women?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1218", "question": "Who is the author of Germinal and also the director of And the Ship Sails On?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1219", "question": "Who is the author of The Dragons of Eden: Speculations on the Evolution of Human Intelligence and also the director of Ginger and Fred?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1220", "question": "Who is the author of Cosmos and also the director of Saturday Night Live?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1221", "question": "Who is the author of The Demon-Haunted World and also the director of The Prince of Tides?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1222", "question": "Who is the author of Broca's Brain: Reflections on the Romance of Science and also the director of Inglourious Basterds?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1223", "question": "Who is the author of L'Argent and also the director of I Vitelloni?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1224", "question": "Who is the author of Le Ventre de Paris and also the director of The White Sheik?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1225", "question": "Who is the author of Citizendium and also the director of Love in the City?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1226", "question": "Who is the author of La Curée and also the director of Day of the Fight?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1227", "question": "Who is the author of Pot-Bouille and also the director of Lost Highway?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1228", "question": "Who is the author of The Ladies' Paradise and also the director of A Woman of Paris?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1229", "question": "Who is the author of Nana and also the director of The Kid?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1230", "question": "Who is the author of Jacques the Fatalist and also the director of A Countess from Hong Kong?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1231", "question": "Who is the author of Encyclopédie and also the director of Limelight?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1232", "question": "Who is the author of Les Soirées de Médan and also the director of Monsieur Verdoux?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1233", "question": "Who is the author of La Bête humaine and also the director of The Tramp?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1234", "question": "Who is the author of J’accuse…! and also the director of Dr. Strangelove?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1235", "question": "Who is the author of L'Assommoir and also the director of Sin City?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1236", "question": "Who is the author of L'Œuvre and also the director of Kill Bill Volume 1?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1237", "question": "Who is both the author of Les Femmes Savantes and also the screenwriter of The Circus?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1238", "question": "Who is both the author of Le Bourgeois gentilhomme and also the screenwriter of Stalker?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1239", "question": "Who is both the author of The Misanthrope and also the screenwriter of Rigoletto?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1240", "question": "Who is both the author of The School for Wives and also the screenwriter of Day of the Fight?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1241", "question": "Who is both the author of Zaide and also the screenwriter of Lost Highway?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1242", "question": "Who is both the author of Inter caetera and also the screenwriter of One Piece Film: Strong World?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1243", "question": "Who is both the author of Heiligenstadt Testament and also the screenwriter of Getting Acquainted?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1244", "question": "Who is both the author of MMX and also the screenwriter of A Countess from Hong Kong?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1245", "question": "Who is both the author of Ruy Blas and also the screenwriter of A Woman of Paris?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1246", "question": "Who is both the author of La Légende des siècles and also the screenwriter of Antony and Cleopatra?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1247", "question": "Who is both the author of Les Orientales and also the screenwriter of A Midsummer Night's Dream?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1248", "question": "Who is both the author of Une Page d'amour and also the screenwriter of SpongeBob SquarePants?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1249", "question": "Who is both the author of The Fortune of the Rougons and also the screenwriter of The Lovely Bones?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1250", "question": "Who is both the author of Hernani and also the screenwriter of Braindead?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1251", "question": "Who is both the author of Sermon on the Mount and also the screenwriter of Mulholland Drive?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1252", "question": "Who is both the author of Les Précieuses ridicules and also the screenwriter of The Elephant Man?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1253", "question": "Who is both the author of Monetae cudendae ratio and also the screenwriter of Pay Day?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1254", "question": "Who is both the author of Supplément au voyage de Bougainville and also the screenwriter of The Floorwalker?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1255", "question": "Who is both the author of Rameau's Nephew and also the screenwriter of The Great Dictator?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1256", "question": "Who is both the author of La Religieuse and also the screenwriter of The Return of the King?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1257", "question": "Who is the author of The Indiscreet Jewels and also the architect of Palazzo dei Conservatori?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1258", "question": "Who is the author of La Promenade du sceptique and also the architect of Şehzade Mosque?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1259", "question": "Who is the author of De revolutionibus orbium coelestium and also the architect of Sulaymaniyya Takiyya?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1260", "question": "Who is the author of Commentariolus and also the architect of Chigi Chapel?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1261", "question": "Who is the author of Scapin the Schemer and also the architect of Süleymaniye Mosque?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1262", "question": "Who is the author of Monsieur de Pourceaugnac and also the architect of Mehmed Paša Sokolović Bridge?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1263", "question": "Who is the author of Dialogue Concerning the Two Chief World Systems and also the architect of Le Lac villa?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1264", "question": "Who is the author of big lie and also the architect of National Museum of Western Art?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1265", "question": "Who is the author of The Assayer and also the architect of Cabanon de vacances?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1266", "question": "Who is the author of Godesberg Memorandum and also the architect of Sainte Marie de La Tourette?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1267", "question": "Who is the author of Meine Ehre heißt Treue and also the architect of Unité d'habitation?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1268", "question": "Who is the author of Beatitudes and also the architect of Temple Neuf, Metz?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1269", "question": "Who is the author of Nero Decree and also the architect of Palazzo Senatorio?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1270", "question": "Who is the author of Sunsets and also the architect of Sant'Eligio degli Orefici?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1271", "question": "Who is the author of The Imaginary Invalid and also the architect of Villa Giulia?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1272", "question": "Who is the author of The Miser and also the architect of Darwin D. Martin House?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1273", "question": "Who is the author of Treaty of the Confederation of the Rhine and also the architect of Robie House?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1274", "question": "Who is the author of The Last Day of a Condemned Man and also the architect of Marin County Civic Center?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1275", "question": "Who is the author of Hernani and also the architect of Unity Temple?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1276", "question": "Who is the author of Tartuffe and also the architect of Millard House?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1277", "question": "Who is the author of Dom Juan and also the founder of Convention People's Party?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1278", "question": "Who is the author of Le Médecin volant and also the founder of Walt Disney Animation Studios?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1279", "question": "Who is the author of Last will and testament of Adolf Hitler and also the founder of Vox?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1280", "question": "Who is the author of and yet it moves and also the founder of Global Gateway?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1281", "question": "Who is the author of Zweites Buch and also the founder of Tango?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1282", "question": "Who is the author of The Hunchback of Notre Dame and also the founder of Android Runtime?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1283", "question": "Who is the author of Ninety-three and also the founder of Google Pay?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1284", "question": "Who is the author of Constitution of the Duchy of Warsaw and also the founder of Ford Germany?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1285", "question": "Who is the author of The Man Who Laughs and also the founder of Edison Studios?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1286", "question": "Who is the author of Cromwell and also the founder of USC Shoah Foundation?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1287", "question": "Who is the author of Berlin Decree and also the founder of The Walt Disney Company?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1288", "question": "Who is the author of Apple Public Source License and also the founder of The China Press?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1289", "question": "Who is the author of Night and Fog Decree and also the founder of WikiTribune?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1290", "question": "Who is the author of Two New Sciences and also the founder of WT:Social?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1291", "question": "Who is the author of Hitler's Obersalzberg Speech and also the founder of Cadillac?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1292", "question": "Who is the author of Sidereus Nuncius and also the founder of Walt Disney Pictures?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1293", "question": "Who is the author of Law on the Reconstruction of the Reich and also the founder of DreamWorks Animation?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1294", "question": "Who is the author of Parable of the Friend at Night and also the founder of Amblin Entertainment?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1295", "question": "Who is the author of Parable of the Unjust Judge and also the founder of Church of Satan?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1296", "question": "Who is the author of Immortal Beloved and also the founder of Nobel Prize?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1297", "question": "Who is the author of Grammaire égyptienne and also the cast member in Fuck?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1298", "question": "Who is the author of Parable of the Lost Coin and also the cast member in A Prairie Home Companion?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1299", "question": "Who is the author of Parable of the Lost Sheep and also the cast member in It's Complicated?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1300", "question": "Who is the author of Parable of the Sower and also the cast member in The Bridges of Madison County?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1301", "question": "Who is the author of Mein Kampf and also the cast member in The River Wild?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1302", "question": "Who is the author of Julian Assange: Why the world needs WikiLeaks and also the cast member in The Fifth Estate?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1303", "question": "Who is the author of Great Books of the Western World and also the cast member in The Truth According to Wikipedia?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1304", "question": "Who is the author of A Season in Hell and also the cast member in Manhattan?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1305", "question": "Who is the author of Le Bateau ivre and also the cast member in Holocaust?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1306", "question": "Who is the author of Rubberhose and also the cast member in Tomcats?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1307", "question": "Who is the author of WikiLeaks and also the cast member in Real Time with Bill Maher?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1308", "question": "Who is the author of Os Lusíadas and also the cast member in Primary Colors?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1309", "question": "Who is the author of Just Kids and also the cast member in By the People: The Election of Barack Obama?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1310", "question": "Who is the author of Cypherpunks and also the cast member in No End in Sight?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1311", "question": "Who is the author of Les Misérables and also the cast member in The War You Don't See?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1312", "question": "Who is the author of Roméo et Juliette and also the cast member in Delivery Man?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1313", "question": "Who is the author of Comme il vous plaira and also the cast member in Out of Time?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1314", "question": "Who is the author of Toilers of the mer and also the cast member in The Blank Generation?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1315", "question": "Who is the author of Cypherpunks and also the cast member in Song to Song?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1316", "question": "Who is the author of Roméo et Juliette and also the cast member in The Power of Good: Nicholas Winton?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1317", "question": "Who is the member of the sports team Juventus FC and also works as the editor for Zeitschrift fuer Papyrologie und Epigraphik?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1318", "question": "Who is the member of the sports team U.C. Sampdoria and also works as the editor for Prosopographisches Lexikon der Palaiologenzeit?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1319", "question": "Who is the member of the sports team Amsterdam and also works as the editor for Oesterreichisches Musiklexikon?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1320", "question": "Who is the member of the sports team Bolivia and also works as the editor for Crell's Annalen?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1321", "question": "Who is the member of the sports team Utrecht and also works as the editor for The Dinosauria?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1322", "question": "Who is the member of the sports team Alaska and also works as the editor for Oriental Stories?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1323", "question": "Who is the member of the sports team AC Milan and also works as the editor for Women's Suffrage Journal?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1324", "question": "Who is the member of the sports team United Arab Emirates and also works as the editor for The Rommel Papers?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1325", "question": "Who is the member of the sports team Nepal and also works as the editor for Hamaas?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1326", "question": "Who is the member of the sports team Pakistan and also works as the editor for E! News?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1327", "question": "Who is the member of the sports team Omsk and also works as the editor for Zeitschrift fuer Kirchengeschichte?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1328", "question": "Who is the member of the sports team Samara and also works as the editor for High Society?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1329", "question": "Who is the member of the sports team Kazan and also works as the editor for Der Stürmer?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1330", "question": "Who is the member of the sports team Atalanta BC and also works as the editor for The Great Wall of China?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1331", "question": "Who is the member of the sports team Hyderabad and also works as the editor for 明文海?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1332", "question": "Who is the member of the sports team Islamabad and also works as the editor for Kicker?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1333", "question": "Who is the member of the sports team New Jersey and also works as the editor for Constitution of the Duchy of Warsaw?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1334", "question": "Who is the member of the sports team Chelyabinsk and also works as the editor for Canon of Kings?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1335", "question": "Who is the member of the sports team Rostov-on-Don and also the founder of The Church of Jesus Christ of Latter-day Saints?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1336", "question": "Who is the member of the sports team Ufa and also the founder of Peking University?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1337", "question": "Who is the member of the sports team Volgograd and also the founder of Diem?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1338", "question": "Who is the member of the sports team Perm and also the founder of Intercommunale d'Inhumation - Intercommunale voor Teraardebestelling?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1339", "question": "Who is the member of the sports team Krasnoyarsk and also the founder of WebGPU?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1340", "question": "Who is the member of the sports team Vladivostok and also the founder of Trilateral Commission?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1341", "question": "Who is the member of the sports team Bologna F.C. 1909 and also the founder of Ford Motor Company?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1342", "question": "Who is the member of the sports team Barcelona and also the founder of State of Palestine?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1343", "question": "Who is the member of the sports team Moscow and also the founder of LaVeyan Satanism?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1344", "question": "Who is the member of the sports team Uttar Pradesh and also the founder of Lunghua Civilian Assembly Center?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1345", "question": "Who is the member of the sports team India and also the founder of PostNord?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1346", "question": "Who is the member of the sports team Moscow Oblast and also the founder of Columbia Country Club Camp?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1347", "question": "Who is the member of the sports team Tallinn and also the founder of The Ahnenerbe?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1348", "question": "Who is the member of the sports team Cagliari Calcio and also the founder of Lebensborn?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1349", "question": "Who is the member of the sports team Bratislava and also the founder of Utrecht University?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1350", "question": "Who is the member of the sports team Odesa and also the founder of El Peruano?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1351", "question": "Who is the member of the sports team ACF Fiorentina and also the founder of DreamWorks Records?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1352", "question": "Who is the member of the sports team Genoa CFC and also the founder of InterContinental?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1353", "question": "Who is the member of the sports team Catania F.C. and also the founder of Amblimation?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1354", "question": "Who is the member of the sports team A.C. ChievoVerona and also the founder of Batkivshchyna?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1355", "question": "Who is the director of Shanghaied and also the editor of Theological Studies?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1356", "question": "Who is the director of The Mirror and also the editor of The Londoner?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1357", "question": "Who is the director of The Steamroller and the Violin and also the editor of The Criterion?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1358", "question": "Who is the director of Police and also the editor of Adagia?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1359", "question": "Who is the director of Sunnyside and also the editor of Capital: A Critique of Political Economy?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1360", "question": "Who is the director of Easy Street and also the editor of Black Orpheus?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1361", "question": "Who is the director of The New Janitor and also the editor of Des Knaben Wunderhorn?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1362", "question": "Who is the director of Pulp Fiction and also the editor of Gaia Data Release 1?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1363", "question": "Who is the director of Empire and also the editor of De revolutionibus orbium coelestium?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1364", "question": "Who is the director of The Lord of the Rings: The Two Towers and also the editor of Annual Review of Astronomy and Astrophysics?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1365", "question": "Who is the director of Lolita and also the editor of Byzantinische Zeitschrift?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1366", "question": "Who is the director of Barry Lyndon and also the editor of Deutsche Entomologische Zeitschrift?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1367", "question": "Who is the director of Lumière and Company and also the editor of Fauna Japonica?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1368", "question": "Who is the director of Django Unchained and also the editor of Stoicorum Veterum Fragmenta?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1369", "question": "Who is the director of The Other Boleyn Girl and also the editor of Annals of Physics?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1370", "question": "Who is the director of Layer Cake and also the editor of Sacred Books of the East?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1371", "question": "Who is the director of Buzz Lightyear of Star Command and also the editor of Glottolog?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1372", "question": "Who is the director of Ivan's Childhood and also the editor of The Children of Húrin?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1373", "question": "Who is the director of The Floorwalker and also the editor of Unfinished Tales?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1374", "question": "Who is the director of Blue Velvet and also the editor of Soviet Encyclopedic Dictionary?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1375", "question": "Who is the director of Paths of Glory and also the founder of The People of Freedom?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1376", "question": "Who is the director of The Killing and also the founder of Padania national football team?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1377", "question": "Who is the director of Mulholland Drive and also the founder of Gestapo?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1378", "question": "Who is the director of The Elephant Man and also the founder of United States Department of Energy?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1379", "question": "Who is the director of Four Rooms and also the founder of Reich Main Security Office?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1380", "question": "Who is the director of Death Proof and also the founder of Sicherheitsdienst?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1381", "question": "Who is the director of The Haunted World of El Superbeasto and also the founder of Mercury Theatre?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1382", "question": "Who is the director of Wild at Heart and also the founder of The Secret Policeman's Balls?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1383", "question": "Who is the director of Dune and also the founder of House of Al Sabah?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1384", "question": "Who is the director of Spartacus and also the founder of Bank of North America?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1385", "question": "Who is the director of My Best Friend's Birthday and also the founder of United States Department of Education?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1386", "question": "Who is the director of Head of State and also the founder of Satellite Sentinel Project?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1387", "question": "Who is the director of The Hobbit trilogy and also the founder of Dynamit Nobel?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1388", "question": "Who is the director of Fellini's Casanova and also the founder of Hauteville family?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1389", "question": "Who is the director of Orchestra Rehearsal and also the founder of Tashilhunpo Monastery?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1390", "question": "Who is the director of Amarcord and also the founder of Uffizi Gallery?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1391", "question": "Who is the director of Magical Mystery Tour and also the founder of Edison Records?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1392", "question": "Who is the director of Kill Bill Volume 2 and also the founder of Edison Illuminating Company?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1393", "question": "Who is the director of Camp and also the founder of All-African People's Revolutionary Party?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1394", "question": "Who is the director of The Hobbit: The Battle of the Five Armies and also the founder of Ecumenical Patriarchate of Constantinople?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1395", "question": "Who is the director of Satyricon and also the cast member in Steve Jobs?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1396", "question": "Who is the director of The Birds and also the cast member in Citizenfour?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1397", "question": "Who is the director of Boccaccio '70 and also the cast member in Modern Times?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1398", "question": "Who is the director of Juliet of the Spirits and also the cast member in Die Manns – Ein Jahrhundertroman?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1399", "question": "Who is the director of Spirits of the Dead and also the cast member in The Names of Love?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1400", "question": "Who is the director of Batman Dracula and also the cast member in Karl Hess: Toward Liberty?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1401", "question": "Who is the director of The Idle Class and also the cast member in Czechoslovakia 1968?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1402", "question": "Who is the director of Shoulder Arms and also the cast member in Pulp Fiction?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1403", "question": "Who is the director of The Pawnshop and also the cast member in 200 Motels?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1404", "question": "Who is the director of Lonesome Cowboys and also the cast member in Good Bye Lenin!?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1405", "question": "Who is the director of Yentl and also the cast member in Water?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1406", "question": "Who is the director of The Hobbit: The Desolation of Smaug and also the cast member in The Beatles Anthology?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1407", "question": "Who is the director of Vertigo and also the cast member in Monty Python’s Life of Brian?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1408", "question": "Who is the director of Heavenly Creatures and also the cast member in Evening?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1409", "question": "Who is the director of Bad Taste and also the cast member in Music of the Heart?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1410", "question": "Who is the director of Eat and also the cast member in Ice and the Sky?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1411", "question": "Who is the director of Flesh for Frankenstein and also the cast member in The Yes Men Are Revolting?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1412", "question": "Who is the director of Larry Crowne and also the cast member in Snowden?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1413", "question": "Who is the director of Jackie Brown and also the cast member in Pitch Perfect 2?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1414", "question": "Who is the director of Rope and also the cast member in Getting Acquainted?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1415", "question": "Who is the screenwriter of Ultimate Avengers 2 and also the composer of Serenade No. 6?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1416", "question": "Who is the screenwriter of Braddock: Missing in Action III and also the composer of Adagio in E for Violin and Orchestra?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1417", "question": "Who is the screenwriter of Hibernatus and also the composer of Don Giovanni?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1418", "question": "Who is the screenwriter of That Thing You Do! and also the composer of Apollo et Hyacinthus?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1419", "question": "Who is the screenwriter of The Immigrant and also the composer of Zaide?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1420", "question": "Who is the screenwriter of A King in New York and also the composer of Land der Berge, Land am Strome?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1421", "question": "Who is the screenwriter of A Night in the Show and also the composer of Twelve Variations on \"Ah vous dirai-je, Maman\"?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1422", "question": "Who is the screenwriter of Hudson Hawk and also the composer of Oedipus Rex?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1423", "question": "Who is the screenwriter of Larry Crowne and also the composer of Rondo in B-flat for Violin and Orchestra?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1424", "question": "Who is the screenwriter of Walker, Texas Ranger and also the composer of Sinfonia Concertante for Violin, Viola and Orchestra?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1425", "question": "Who is the screenwriter of The Big Restaurant and also the composer of A Musical Joke?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1426", "question": "Who is the screenwriter of Rabbits and also the composer of Rondo in C for Violin and Orchestra?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1427", "question": "Who is the screenwriter of Invasion U.S.A. and also the composer of Haydn Quartets?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1428", "question": "Who is the screenwriter of Head of State and also the composer of Ein Mädchen oder Weibchen?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1429", "question": "Who is the screenwriter of Limelight and also the composer of Violin Sonata No. 21?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1430", "question": "Who is the screenwriter of The Tramp and also the composer of Der Vogelfänger bin ich ja?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1431", "question": "Who is the screenwriter of In the Park and also the composer of Dies Bildnis ist bezaubernd schön?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1432", "question": "Who is the screenwriter of Sunnyside and also the composer of Piano Concerto No. 10?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1433", "question": "Who is the screenwriter of The New Janitor and also the composer of Piano Sonata No. 16?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1434", "question": "Who is the screenwriter of The Fatal Mallet and also the composer of Divertimento No. 1?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1435", "question": "Who is the screenwriter of Cruel, Cruel Love and also the architect of Taliesin West?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1436", "question": "Who is the screenwriter of Inland Empire and also the architect of Unité d'habitation of Briey?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1437", "question": "Who is the screenwriter of Je t'aime moi non plus and also the architect of Town hall of Boulogne-Billancourt?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1438", "question": "Who is the screenwriter of A Day's Pleasure and also the architect of Government Museum and Art Gallery, Chandigarh?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1439", "question": "Who is the screenwriter of Triple Trouble and also the architect of Villa Jeanneret-Perret?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1440", "question": "Who is the screenwriter of By the Sea and also the architect of Villa La Roche?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1441", "question": "Who is the screenwriter of The Idle Class and also the architect of Rüstem Pasha Mosque?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1442", "question": "Who is the screenwriter of Shoulder Arms and also the architect of Porta Pia?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1443", "question": "Who is the screenwriter of Kid Auto Races at Venice and also the architect of Villa Madama?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1444", "question": "Who is the screenwriter of Band of Brothers and also the architect of Usonia?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1445", "question": "Who is the screenwriter of Nineteen Eighty-Four and also the architect of Winslow House?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1446", "question": "Who is the screenwriter of The Rock and also the architect of Frank Lloyd Wright Home and Studio?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1447", "question": "Who is the screenwriter of From Dusk till Dawn and also the architect of Rookery Building?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1448", "question": "Who is the screenwriter of A Dog's Life and also the architect of Hollyhock House?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1449", "question": "Who is the screenwriter of The Pawnshop and also the architect of Larkin Administration Building?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1450", "question": "Who is the screenwriter of Nostalghia and also the architect of Johnson Wax Headquarters?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1451", "question": "Who is the screenwriter of Django Unchained and also the architect of Molla Çelebi Mosque?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1452", "question": "Who is the screenwriter of Bad Taste and also the architect of Haseki Hürrem Sultan Hamamı?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1453", "question": "Who is the screenwriter of Industrial Symphony No. 1 and also the architect of Seven Saints Church?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1454", "question": "Who is the screenwriter of Magical Mystery Tour and also the architect of Atik Valide Mosque?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1455", "question": "Who is the screenwriter of Ultimate Avengers and also the employer of Arnnon Geshuri?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1456", "question": "Who is the screenwriter of Pilot and also the employer of Michael Stevens?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1457", "question": "Who is the screenwriter of The Bank and also the employer of Mike Pinkerton?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1458", "question": "Who is the screenwriter of Double Trouble and also the employer of Kōichirō Tsujino?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1459", "question": "Who is the screenwriter of La Gioconda and also the employer of Peter Sutherland?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1460", "question": "Who is the screenwriter of There Will Be No Leave Today and also the employer of Jan Egeland?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1461", "question": "Who is the screenwriter of The Knockout and also the employer of Misa Telefoni Retzlaff?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1462", "question": "Who is the screenwriter of The Cure and also the employer of Ivan Šimonović?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1463", "question": "Who is the screenwriter of Twenty Minutes of Love and also the employer of Karan Bhatia?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1464", "question": "Who is the screenwriter of Logan's War: Bound by Honor and also the employer of Jens Eilstrup Rasmussen?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1465", "question": "Who is the screenwriter of Keep the Aspidistra Flying and also the employer of Crystal Lee?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1466", "question": "Who is the screenwriter of It Happened at the World's Fair and also the employer of Françoise Brougher?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1467", "question": "Who is the screenwriter of The Five Doctors and also the employer of Christine Marzano?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1468", "question": "Who is the screenwriter of The Master and Margarita and also the employer of Carol Bellamy?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1469", "question": "Who is the screenwriter of Pulse and also the employer of Celso Amorim?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1470", "question": "Who is the screenwriter of Natural Born Killers and also the employer of Patrick Pichette?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1471", "question": "Who is the screenwriter of The French as Seen By... and also the employer of Omid Kordestani?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1472", "question": "Who is the screenwriter of Nineteen Eighty-Four and also the employer of Peiter Zatko?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1473", "question": "Who is the screenwriter of Kingsman: The Secret Service and also the employer of Paul Buchheit?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1474", "question": "Who is the screenwriter of It's Pat and also the employer of Jef Raskin?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1475", "question": "Who is the screenwriter for It's a SpongeBob Christmas! and also the founder of Assyrian Church of the East?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1476", "question": "Who is the screenwriter for Full Measure and also the founder of Five Star Movement?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1477", "question": "Who is the screenwriter for Laughing Gas and also the founder of Future and Freedom?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1478", "question": "Who is the screenwriter for Her Friend the Bandit and also the founder of Walt Disney Studios?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1479", "question": "Who is the screenwriter for The Debt and also the founder of Din-e Ilahi?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1480", "question": "Who is the screenwriter for Missing in Action and also the founder of Kashag?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1481", "question": "Who is the screenwriter for Twin Peaks: Fire Walk with Me and also the founder of Laugh-O-Gram Studio?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1482", "question": "Who is the screenwriter for Empire and also the founder of Epicureanism?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1483", "question": "Who is the screenwriter for Un Chien Andalou and also the founder of Church of the East?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1484", "question": "Who is the screenwriter for Lolita and also the founder of Reich Central Office for the Combating of Homosexuality and Abortion?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1485", "question": "Who is the screenwriter for The Killing and also the founder of Italy of Values?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1486", "question": "Who is the screenwriter for The Hobbit: The Desolation of Smaug and also the founder of Lega Nord?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1487", "question": "Who is the screenwriter for Grindhouse and also the founder of Mesta?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1488", "question": "Who is the screenwriter for Killer's Kiss and also the founder of Bran Castle?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1489", "question": "Who is the screenwriter for Fear and Desire and also the founder of Order of Pius IX?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1490", "question": "Who is the screenwriter for Darkened Room and also the founder of Militant League for German Culture?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1491", "question": "Who is the screenwriter for Équateur and also the founder of The Elders?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1492", "question": "Who is the screenwriter for A Certain Smile and also the founder of International Federation for Housing and Planning?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1493", "question": "Who is the screenwriter for Night Magic and also the founder of Syncopy Inc.?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1494", "question": "Who is the screenwriter for Henry IV and also the founder of Company of One Hundred Associates?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1495", "question": "Who is the architect of Mihrimah Üsküdar Mosque and also the composer of Mozart horn concertos?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1496", "question": "Who is the architect of Frida Kahlo Museum and also the composer of Clarinet Concerto in A major, K. 622?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1497", "question": "Who is the architect of Sukhna Lake and also the composer of Lucio Silla?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1498", "question": "Who is the architect of Immeuble Molitor and also the composer of Ave verum corpus?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1499", "question": "Who is the architect of Villa Jeanneret and also the composer of Maurerische Trauermusik?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1500", "question": "Who is the architect of Dom-ino House and also the composer of Suzanne's Career?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1501", "question": "Who is the architect of Palace of Assembly and also the composer of The Best of Youth?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1502", "question": "Who is the architect of Secretariat Building and also the composer of Die Schuldigkeit des ersten Gebots?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1503", "question": "Who is the architect of United Nations Secretariat Building and also the composer of String Quartet No. 2?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1504", "question": "Who is the architect of Sinan Pasha Mosque and also the composer of Flute Concertos (Mozart)?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1505", "question": "Who is the architect of Şemsi Pasha Mosque and also the composer of Bei Männern, welche Liebe fühlen?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1506", "question": "Who is the architect of Zal Mahmud Pasha Mosque and also the composer of Heinrich?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1507", "question": "Who is the architect of Sokollu Mehmed Pasha I Mosque and also the composer of Mozart's Twelfth Mass, K. Anh. 232?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1508", "question": "Who is the architect of Yodokō Guest House and also the composer of Oboe Quartet?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1509", "question": "Who is the architect of Herbert and Katherine Jacobs First House and also the composer of A Man Escaped?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1510", "question": "Who is the architect of V. C. Morris Gift Shop and also the composer of Vergeßt Mozart?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1511", "question": "Who is the architect of Storer House and also the composer of Piano Concerto No. 21 in C major?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1512", "question": "Who is the architect of Weltzheimer/Johnson House and also the composer of Piano Concerto No.20 in D minor, K.466?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1513", "question": "Who is the architect of Unity Chapel and also the composer of The Marriage of Figaro?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1514", "question": "Who is the architect of Würzburg Residence and also the composer of Violin Concerto No. 5?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1515", "question": "Who is the architect of Semperoper and also the editor of Profil?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1516", "question": "Who is the architect of St. Vitus Cathedral and also the editor of Siete Partidas?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1517", "question": "Who is the architect of Kanuni Bridge and also the editor of ACS Chemical Biology?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1518", "question": "Who is the architect of Selim Üsküdar Mosque and also the editor of The Limits to Growth?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1519", "question": "Who is the architect of Piyale Pasha Mosque and also the editor of Giant-Size X-Men #1?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1520", "question": "Who is the architect of Louis Sullivan Bungalow and also the editor of Vala, or The Four Zoas?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1521", "question": "Who is the architect of Monona Terrace and also the editor of Decretals of Gregory IX?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1522", "question": "Who is the architect of Blue Sky Mausoleum and also the editor of The Nine Chapters on the Mathematical Art?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1523", "question": "Who is the architect of Crystal Heights and also the editor of Swords and Sorcery?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1524", "question": "Who is the architect of Arthur Heurtley House and also the editor of Ryōjin Hishō?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1525", "question": "Who is the architect of American System-Built Homes and also the editor of Mother Earth?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1526", "question": "Who is the architect of Annunciation Greek Orthodox Church and also the editor of The New Freewoman?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1527", "question": "Who is the architect of Price Tower and also the editor of Encyclopedic Dictionary of Mathematics?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1528", "question": "Who is the architect of Barnsdall Art Park and also the editor of Oceanic Linguistics?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1529", "question": "Who is the architect of Cenabi Ahmet Paşa Mosque and also the editor of Great Soviet Encyclopedia?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1530", "question": "Who is the architect of Haseki Sultan Mosque and also the editor of The Twelve Dancing Princesses?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1531", "question": "Who is the architect of Muradiye Mosque and also the editor of Flora Iranica?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1532", "question": "Who is the architect of Hôtel de Ville de Lyon and also the editor of Taxonomy database of the U.S. National Center for Biotechnology Information?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1533", "question": "Who is the architect of Graycliff and also the editor of Der Orchideengarten?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1534", "question": "Who is the architect of Gammage Memorial Auditorium and also the editor of Freiheit?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1535", "question": "Who is the architect that works for Noam Shazeer and also the employer of Gemäldegalerie Alte Meister?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1536", "question": "Who is the architect that works for Brewster Kahle and also the employer of Kunstsammlung Nordrhein-Westfalen?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1537", "question": "Who is the architect that works for Bill Budge and also the employer of Maximilianeum?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1538", "question": "Who is the architect that works for Hugo Barra and also the employer of Charles Bridge?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1539", "question": "Who is the architect that works for Behdad Esfahbod and also the employer of Rüstem Pasha Caravanserai?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1540", "question": "Who is the architect that works for Manu Cornet and also the employer of Mihrimah Edirnekapı Mosque?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1541", "question": "Who is the architect that works for Bill Maris and also the employer of Defterdar Mosque?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1542", "question": "Who is the architect that works for Oriol Vinyals and also the employer of Maximilianstraße?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1543", "question": "Who is the architect that works for Ellen Hancock and also the employer of Ullevål University Hospital?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1544", "question": "Who is the architect that works for James A. Bell and also the employer of Nidaros Cathedral?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1545", "question": "Who is the architect that works for Fred D. Anderson and also the employer of Grand Trianon?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1546", "question": "Who is the architect that works for Donald Norman and also the employer of Hamburg City Hall?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1547", "question": "Who is the architect that works for Scott Forstall and also the employer of Wieskirche?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1548", "question": "Who is the architect that works for Tony Fadell and also the employer of Vaduz Cathedral?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1549", "question": "Who is the architect that works for Chris DiBona and also the employer of Palace of Versailles?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1550", "question": "Who is the architect that works for Susan Kare and also the employer of Rubenshuis?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1551", "question": "Who is the architect that works for Michael Spindler and also the employer of Banya Bashi Mosque?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1552", "question": "Who is the architect that works for Hiroshi Lockheimer and also the employer of Church of the Gesù?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1553", "question": "Who is the architect that works for Bret Taylor and also the employer of Asian Art Museum of San Francisco?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1554", "question": "Who is the architect that works for Malou Aamund and also the employer of Apostolic Palace?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1555", "question": "Who is the architect of Devil's Bridge and also the cast member in A Countess from Hong Kong?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1556", "question": "Who is the architect of Santa Maria presso San Satiro and also the cast member in A Woman of Paris?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1557", "question": "Who is the architect of Pavia Cathedral and also the cast member in The People Speak?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1558", "question": "Who is the architect of Hôtel Ritz Paris and also the cast member in The Upsetter?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1559", "question": "Who is the architect of Berlin Cathedral and also the cast member in It Happened at the World's Fair?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1560", "question": "Who is the architect of Living Room from the Francis W. Little House: Windows and paneling and also the cast member in When You're Strange?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1561", "question": "Who is the architect of Samuel Freeman House and also the cast member in Girls! Girls! Girls!?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1562", "question": "Who is the architect of Quartiers Modernes Frugès and also the cast member in The Road to Bresson?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1563", "question": "Who is the architect of Unité d'Habitation de Marseille and also the cast member in Neil Young Journeys?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1564", "question": "Who is the architect of Carpenter Center for the Visual Arts and also the cast member in Paradox?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1565", "question": "Who is the architect of Rusakov Workers' Club and also the cast member in 20 Feet from Stardom?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1566", "question": "Who is the architect of Curutchet House and also the cast member in Think Like a Man Too?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1567", "question": "Who is the architect of Abattoirs de la Mouche and also the cast member in An Inconvenient Sequel: Truth to Power?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1568", "question": "Who is the architect of Villa Schwob and also the cast member in Pope Francis: A Man of His Word?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1569", "question": "Who is the architect of Villa Fallet and also the cast member in The Putin Interviews?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1570", "question": "Who is the architect of manufacture Claude-et-Duval and also the cast member in America: The Story of Us?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1571", "question": "Who is the architect of Open Hand Monument and also the cast member in Planet of the Humans?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1572", "question": "Who is the architect of Wernigerode Castle and also the cast member in Help!?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1573", "question": "Who is the architect of Hufeisensiedlung and also the cast member in Blue Hawaii?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1574", "question": "Who is the architect of Przebendowski Palace and also the cast member in The Last Mimzy?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1575", "question": "Who is the composer of Violin Concerto No. 4 and also the editor for Oxford Book of English Verse?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1576", "question": "Who is the composer of Oboe Concerto and also the editor for The Firebird and Princess Vasilisa?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1577", "question": "Who is the composer of Symphony No. 31 and also the editor for Vasilisa the Priest's Daughter?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1578", "question": "Who is the composer of Symphony No. 29 and also the editor for 1967–1970?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1579", "question": "Who is the composer of Symphony No. 32 and also the editor for Gedanken und Erinnerungen?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1580", "question": "Who is the composer of String Quintet No. 4 and also the editor for Atmospheric Chemistry and Physics?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1581", "question": "Who is the composer of Viennese Quartets and also the editor for Polar Star?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1582", "question": "Who is the composer of Group Portrait with Lady and also the editor for Free Software, Free Society?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1583", "question": "Who is the composer of O zittre nicht, mein lieber Sohn and also the editor for The Silmarillion?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1584", "question": "Who is the composer of Milanese Quartets and also the editor for Bach-Werke-Verzeichnis?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1585", "question": "Who is the composer of Half a Life and also the editor for The Letters of J. R. R. Tolkien?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1586", "question": "Who is the composer of Piano Concerto No. 24 in C minor and also the editor for The English Hymnal?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1587", "question": "Who is the composer of Piano Concerto No. 23 in A major and also the editor for Songs of Praise?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1588", "question": "Who is the composer of Violin Sonata No. 27 and also the editor for Otechestvennaia istoriia?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1589", "question": "Who is the composer of Clarinet Quintet and also the editor for Otechestvennye Zapiski?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1590", "question": "Who is the composer of Violin Sonata No. 35 and also the editor for History of Ming?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1591", "question": "Who is the composer of Così fan tutte and also the editor for Great Soviet Encyclopedia (1969–1978)?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1592", "question": "Who is the composer of Piano Concerto No. 19 and also the editor for The Guardian of Education?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1593", "question": "Who is the composer of Piano Concertos Nos. 1–4 and also the editor for The Egoist?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1594", "question": "Who is the composer of Mozart piano concertos and also the editor for Siberian Mathematical Journal?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1595", "question": "Who is the composer of known for Face to Face and also the founder of Section Eight Productions?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1596", "question": "Who is the composer of known for Piano Concerto No. 9 and also the founder of Ganden Sumtseling Monastery?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1597", "question": "Who is the composer of known for Coronation Mass and also the founder of National Democratic Party?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1598", "question": "Who is the composer of known for Great Mass in C minor and also the founder of Lightstorm Entertainment?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1599", "question": "Who is the composer of known for Leck mich im Arsch and also the founder of Lviv National Museum?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1600", "question": "Who is the composer of known for Uzak and also the founder of Conservatoire Rachmaninoff?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1601", "question": "Who is the composer of known for Symphony No. 35 and also the founder of Organization of Modern Extreme Grappling Arts?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1602", "question": "Who is the composer of known for Symphony No. 36 and also the founder of Imprimerie Nationale?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1603", "question": "Who is the composer of known for Symphony No. 34 and also the founder of Maison Carrée?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1604", "question": "Who is the composer of known for Symphony No. 33 and also the founder of Volkhov Front?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1605", "question": "Who is the composer of known for Bassoon Concerto and also the founder of World Habitat Day?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1606", "question": "Who is the composer of known for Concerto for Flute, Harp, and Orchestra and also the founder of Mont Pelerin Society?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1607", "question": "Who is the composer of known for Colonel Chabert and also the founder of Grand Duchy of Tuscany?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1608", "question": "Who is the composer of known for Der Hölle Rache kocht in meinem Herzen and also the founder of 1st Far Eastern Front?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1609", "question": "Who is the composer of known for Der Stein der Weisen and also the founder of Digital Domain?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1610", "question": "Who is the composer of known for Die Entführung aus dem Serail and also the founder of Congregation for the Oriental Churches?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1611", "question": "Who is the composer of known for Requiem and also the founder of Malkata?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1612", "question": "Who is the composer of known for Shéhérazade and also the founder of Schutzmannschaft?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1613", "question": "Who is the composer of known for Piano Concerto for the Left Hand and also the founder of Ford Australia?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1614", "question": "Who is the composer of known for Daphnis et Chloé and also the founder of Henry Ford Company?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1615", "question": "Who is the composer of String Quartet and also the cast member in Follow That Dream?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1616", "question": "Who is the composer of Jeux d'eau and also the cast member in Wild in the Country?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1617", "question": "Who is the composer of Fin ch' han dal vino and also the cast member in Roustabout?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1618", "question": "Who is the composer of Il mio tesoro and also the cast member in Dawn of the Planet of the Apes?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1619", "question": "Who is the composer of Inventions and Sinfonias and also the cast member in Ronaldo?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1620", "question": "Who is the composer of In diesen heil'gen Hallen and also the cast member in Uncle Howard?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1621", "question": "Who is the composer of Piano Sonata No. 7 and also the cast member in Before the Flood?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1622", "question": "Who is the composer of Sonata for Two Pianos in D major and also the cast member in Die Hard?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1623", "question": "Who is the composer of La tartine de beurre and also the cast member in Die Hard 2?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1624", "question": "Who is the composer of Piano Sonata in F major, K. 547a and also the cast member in Risk?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1625", "question": "Who is the composer of Non più andrai and also the cast member in Francofonia?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1626", "question": "Who is the composer of String Duo No. 1 and also the cast member in I Am Not Your Negro?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1627", "question": "Who is the composer of Violin Sonata No. 17 and also the cast member in The Secret Scripture?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1628", "question": "Who is the composer of Là ci darem la mano and also the cast member in Death Scenes?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1629", "question": "Who is the composer of String Duo No. 2 and also the cast member in The Floorwalker?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1630", "question": "Who is the composer of Symphony No. 39 and also the cast member in The Great Dictator?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1631", "question": "Who is the composer of Symphony No. 38 and also the cast member in Asterix at the Olympic Games?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1632", "question": "Who is the composer of Exsultate, jubilate and also the cast member in Loving You?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1633", "question": "Who is the composer of La clemenza di Tito and also the cast member in I Served the King of England?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1634", "question": "Who is the composer of String Quartet No. 19 and also the cast member in The Kid?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1635", "question": "Who is the editor of Kolokol and also the cast member in Burlesque on Carmen?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1636", "question": "Who is the editor of Encyclopedia of the Holocaust and also the cast member in A Film Johnnie?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1637", "question": "Who is the editor of Heroes of the Resistance and also the cast member in iParty with Victorious?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1638", "question": "Who is the editor of Stuart Hall and also the cast member in iCarly?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1639", "question": "Who is the editor of The Dial and also the cast member in Louisa?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1640", "question": "Who is the editor of Fragmente der griechischen Historiker and also the cast member in Good Night, and Good Luck.?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1641", "question": "Who is the editor of Jüdische Allgemeine and also the cast member in The Wonderful Horrible Life of Leni Riefenstahl?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1642", "question": "Who is the editor of Miscellaneous notes from hundreds of schools of classics and history and also the cast member in From Hell to Victory?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1643", "question": "Who is the editor of Unique Ingredient Identifier and also the cast member in December 7th?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1644", "question": "Who is the editor of Austrian Academy of Sciences and also the cast member in American Masters?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1645", "question": "Who is the editor of Emma and also the cast member in A Hard Day's Night?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1646", "question": "Who is the editor of Die Fragmente der Vorsokratiker and also the cast member in Candy?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1647", "question": "Who is the editor of Playboy and also the cast member in Caveman?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1648", "question": "Who is the editor of First Book of Kings and also the cast member in Die Hard with a Vengeance?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1649", "question": "Who is the editor of Annals of Mathematics and also the cast member in The Fifth Element?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1650", "question": "Who is the editor of Handbook of Mathematical Functions with Formulas, Graphs, and Mathematical Tables and also the cast member in A Million Ways to Die in the West?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1651", "question": "Who is the editor of International Council Correspondence and also the cast member in The Interview?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1652", "question": "Who is the editor of Enneads and also the cast member in The Sixth Sense?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1653", "question": "Who is the editor of Polar star and also the cast member in 12 Monkeys?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1654", "question": "Who is the editor of The Tatler and also the cast member in My Name Is Earl?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1655", "question": "Who is the editor for Dongguk Tonggam and also the founder of Disneyland Resort?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1656", "question": "Who is the editor for Paulys Realenzyklopädie der klassischen Altertumswissenschaft and also the founder of National University of Trujillo?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1657", "question": "Who is the editor for Allgemeine musikalische Zeitung and also the founder of Ford Motor Company of Canada?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1658", "question": "Who is the editor for LEF and also the founder of Single European Sky ATM Research?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1659", "question": "Who is the editor for Westminster Review and also the founder of Basilica of Sant'Ambrogio?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1660", "question": "Who is the editor for Skeptic and also the founder of Château Gaillard?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1661", "question": "Who is the editor for Die Welt and also the founder of Tennman Records?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1662", "question": "Who is the editor for Man'yōshū and also the founder of United National Movement?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1663", "question": "Who is the editor for Shin Kokin Wakashū and also the founder of DreamWorks Television?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1664", "question": "Who is the editor for Kokin Wakashū and also the founder of University of Cartagena?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1665", "question": "Who is the editor for Ruijū Kokushi and also the founder of Accra Evening News?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1666", "question": "Who is the editor for Spixiana and also the founder of Henry Ford Health System?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1667", "question": "Who is the editor for Table Talk and also the founder of Museon Arlaten?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1668", "question": "Who is the editor for Völkischer Beobachter and also the founder of Organization of Afro-American Unity?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1669", "question": "Who is the editor for Guanzi and also the founder of Malpaso Productions?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1670", "question": "Who is the editor for Subaru and also the founder of Société des poètes français?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1671", "question": "Who is the editor for Focus and also the founder of Muslim Mosque?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1672", "question": "Who is the editor for Unsere Zeit and also the founder of Aqua Virgo?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1673", "question": "Who is the editor for Mathematical Notes and also the founder of Basilica of San Lorenzo?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1674", "question": "Who is the editor for Hyakunin Shūka and also the founder of La Nouvelle Revue française?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1675", "question": "Who is the employer of Chade-Meng Tan and also the founder of Edison Manufacturing Company?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1676", "question": "Who is the employer of Robert Love and also the founder of Thomas A. Edison, Inc.?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1677", "question": "Who is the employer of Ian Hickson and also the founder of Town and Country Planning Association?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1678", "question": "Who is the employer of Steve Jobs and also the founder of Vote Smart?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1679", "question": "Who is the employer of Ashish Vaswani and also the founder of Sinclair Radionics?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1680", "question": "Who is the employer of Dr. Dre and also the founder of Midttrafik?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1681", "question": "Who is the employer of Meredith Whittaker and also the founder of Trigger Street Productions?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1682", "question": "Who is the employer of Vasily Nebenzya and also the founder of Haupttreuhandstelle Ost?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1683", "question": "Who is the employer of Ferdinand Oyono and also the founder of St. Elisabeth's Church?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1684", "question": "Who is the employer of Steve Wozniak and also the founder of Design Council?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1685", "question": "Who is the employer of Tim Harford and also the founder of Library Journal?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1686", "question": "Who is the employer of Keiji Fukuda and also the founder of Smokehouse Pictures?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1687", "question": "Who is the employer of Ibrahim Gambari and also the founder of Intergovernmental Panel on Climate Change?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1688", "question": "Who is the employer of Ole Henrik Magga and also the founder of The Giving Pledge?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1689", "question": "Who is the employer of Maciej Stachowiak and also the founder of 4th Ukrainian Front?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1690", "question": "Who is the employer of Phil Schiller and also the founder of International Day of Democracy?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1691", "question": "Who is the employer of Craig Federighi and also the founder of Lega Lombarda?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1692", "question": "Who is the employer of Angela Ahrendts and also the founder of 1st Baltic Front?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1693", "question": "Who is the employer of Nancy R. Heinen and also the founder of Il Popolo d'Italia?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1694", "question": "Who is the employer of Sina Tamaddon and also the founder of Al-Quds Open University?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1695", "question": "Who is the employer of Robert J. Pera and also the cast member of The 13th?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1696", "question": "Who is the employer of Robert Brunner and also the cast member of The Prestige?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1697", "question": "Who is the employer of Charles Woodruff Yost and also the cast member of Vanilla Sky?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1698", "question": "Who is the employer of Christian Friis Bach and also the cast member of Zero Days?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1699", "question": "Who is the employer of Natalie Villalobos and also the cast member of Backstabbing for Beginners?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1700", "question": "Who is the employer of Evangelista Torricelli and also the cast member of Patriots Day?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1701", "question": "Who is the employer of Jeff Robbin and also the cast member of Blindman?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1702", "question": "Who is the employer of Roger Powell and also the cast member of Magical Mystery Tour?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1703", "question": "Who is the employer of Jeremy Hammond and also the cast member of The Battle of Russia?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1704", "question": "Who is the employer of William Campbell and also the cast member of There Will Be No Leave Today?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1705", "question": "Who is the employer of Mike Markkula and also the cast member of Year of the Horse?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1706", "question": "Who is the employer of Joe Ybarra and also the cast member of Made in Heaven?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1707", "question": "Who is the employer of Yoky Matsuoka and also the cast member of The Clearstream Affair?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1708", "question": "Who is the employer of Lisa P. Jackson and also the cast member of The Compleat Beatles?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1709", "question": "Who is the employer of John Sculley and also the cast member of Singer Presents...Elvis?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1710", "question": "Who is the employer of Ronald Wayne and also the cast member of Once Upon a Honeymoon?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1711", "question": "Who is the employer of Andrew Young and also the cast member of No?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1712", "question": "Who is the employer of Renato Ruggiero and also the cast member of Kissin' Cousins?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1713", "question": "Who is the employer of Jeff Williams and also the cast member of This Is Elvis?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "inter_ua_1714", "question": "Who is the employer of Susan Wagner and also the cast member of Follow This?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}]